Come to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
Dance to the mystery
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So
Let the tarot move
we are king
Monday afternoon. Thank you everybody for being here. We're just getting this show started.
Welcome to the show. Get out and chat. You guys are new members. Ten of our members were out
here yesterday, so I think it's a quiet case. He's not here. I think he might be lurking around.
What are you guys saying?
He's just buying a hamper.
Look at that thing.
Welcome, welcome.
I'm the circus that escaped the asylum.
Where terror cards fly and trolls get tried.
You in the panel verse, baby.
I'm eating, I'm eating.
I have my coffee.
This left you good.
Yeah.
Got linoa in the corner, claws out for lies
Tricks, plot and chaos with those cosmic eyes
Lola squeening on the chair, Rudy got flare
Mumbles in the mix, we don't play fair
Chat blowing up like divine confessions
True bombs drop, no time for confessions
You on logic, we bend it, drama, we mend it
Panel full of chaos, but the vibe's transcending
If a troll wanna bark, we clap back politely
With Andromelius, watchin' nightly
by the psychic cat daddy king of the stream
welcome to psychawakens tv
with truth and madness if the same t
it's a family affair
it's dysfunction supreme
you just woke up in a lucid dream
pan a verse roll call
bring your weirdest takes
we mix logic
with prophecy and cosmic mistakes
alissa in the chat
she a mystery
They swing truth like justice in the moon, like gift is subs
Yeah, the cold keeps growing, community wild, but the energy's flowing
Welcome to Psych Awaken's TV
It's crazy, it's loud, it's bizarre, believe me?
We laugh, we scream, we read the unseen
Father, psych, the cat, daddy, king of the stream
Welcome to Psych Awaken's TV
With truth and madness, if the same tea, it's a family
You just woke up in a lucid dream
Cards flip, candles drip, shadows in the mist
Trolls talk slick, but they cease to exist
We're half chaos, half or a cool flame
And every night's a ritual in Psyche's name
No scripts, no filters, no chill in Psyche
We stream raw truth till the morning light
So grab your tea, grab your mic and vibe
We the strangest family
this ain't youtube this is an underworld's talk show you are now initiating
father psyche is spoken
spoken
both here at the real rg oh randos here what's happening what's happening hi what's up rg what's
I'm a little disappointed today, psyche. I gotta say you know me
No, not you not you see me and Janet made an agreement a few days ago
And I thought I was out of the Janet game. I didn't think I would have to deal with her anymore
You know, and I'm disappointed, you know, we made an agreement and I would leave Janet alone and
You know, we would just be out of each other's lives. I don't even be nice to her if I saw her
Yeah, you sit but I just saw her at Alex chat lying to her trying to weaponize Alex against me
I'm not sure if that goes against agreement, but I kind of think it does. I don't know. I want to put that thought
Janet you wanted to put this behind us, uh, you know for the safety of your family and grandma love and everything we discussed
I'm disappointed. Thank you. What do you think about all this?
I think that um
I think alex was kind of warming up to you a little bit like, you know, i like alex
Other side. Yeah, you know because like anybody gets to know you and like, you know
Well, I don't like Zaya. I don't I think he's a sicko and I know Alex agrees with that
But I also think groovy Jimmy's a sicko. So maybe she she doesn't hasn't done the research on that
You know, I'm not gonna push the narrative
She can do her own research on that
Well, I don't want to fight with Janet anymore. I wanted you know, she's gonna stay away from Groovy Jimmy
We're gonna leave her and her friends alone and that's
She the one from Pittsburgh. Yes, correct. I try to be a nice to her because I show the same home town
She was just a bitch. So yeah, I don't know how far I tried she much like myself
She has an abrasive personality. It maybe it just takes time to get used to her
Right, you and Jan I'm hoping me and Janet could become friends. Honestly a couple you're probably like you know have a similar personality
That could very well be it psych, but I wanted to be out of the Janet trolling game
You know a groupie Jimmy's my true love when it comes to trolling
You know if she didn't insert herself into that we wouldn't have a problem
So she was gonna you know stay away from him and we made a deal
And it hasn't even been 48 hours and she's in Alex's cat trying to get her to talk to me
Say that she got doorknock today, which is a lie that did not happen
Just like she told Tommy that Tommy was talking shit about her and that was a lie
And Alex knew that was a lie. So she's not above lying to weaponize someone else
Yeah
Hey, how come you have a Predator modded, bro, that dude Samman NYC is a fucking Roblox Predator.
Oh.
He's Roblox.
Is that true? I mean, I don't believe that.
That's kind of silly. Come on.
Roblox.
Okay, so it's like people like, I don't know, but I don't, I haven't played that game, but
isn't that just a video game and like, so different ages are playing? I don't know.
I've never seen Samman talk about or play Roblox.
He does play Roblox. Ask him.
Okay, well he played the Roblox. I mean that's like you're allowed to play it in an adult
Be like there's adults that play Pokemon Roblox and you know, yeah, you could be like 50 years old on tiktok, too
It's very normal. No, it's not
You see yeah, I haven't heard him say anything about
Lots of people that play card games though young and old so you can't knock someone for that's not the same
I like Pokemon cards. Yeah, I'm gonna say there's adult Pokemon channels all over the place
Where you can talk and message and talk I get it I know what it is
I've never heard him say anything about Roblox.
So what you're saying is Roblox, there's something there?
Or it's like, there's like, I'm kind of evidence or anything.
I don't want to tell you.
Yeah, there is.
Yeah, I'm like, I'm going to compile it.
Hey, Samman, get on panel.
Come get on panel.
Just talking to people on Roblox about Roblox.
This was beat to get Samman up here?
Is that what it was?
I know.
Not just if he wants his opportunity.
I don't beat.
You could just say it's something to get him up here.
I get it.
I don't think he's playing, I don't think he's playing Roblox, I really don't.
You can say enough to get him up here.
He doesn't mean anything, it's like.
No, no, I don't play card games all the time.
Yo, it's fine.
You know, I like Pokemon cards, I play video games.
The thing is, is Roblox, they're being sued by many, many.
many many people do
How much if you're on the computer, it's like already we have people in chat rooms and people can go in all that stuff
It's not anything that's like
Not already totally sensible to everybody. Yeah, this is beat to get him up here. Come on. I'm pretty good
Yeah, I don't need to beat that dude
All I know about him is that he plays Roblox.
OK, well, that's not a big deal.
I mean, it's like, it does not mean anything.
That's such a ridiculous statement.
All you know about the guy is that he plays Roblox.
Seriously?
Come on.
He's UGO too.
You should go with that.
UGO.
No, UGO's fine.
UGO's fine.
That's a card game.
UGO, you can get him perfectly.
The only thing you know about him is he plays Roblox.
Come on.
Are you on the monkey app?
It's silly.
Brandon, are you on the monkey app?
It just means silly, sir.
Are you on the monkey app, Brandon?
Jimmy's on him, but Groovy Jimmy's on a monkey hat.
I've used it, but no, I'm not on it.
He talks to lots and lots of kids on the
Jimmy's a sicko. He's a sicko
Confirmed what's that lolly too? I did a screen before and what they did is
When I would cam up and connect with somebody and it would be like a little kid or whatever
I would skip but they would take a screenshot the moment that it would connect
That is not going to fucking monkey app
Got a common sense, so you think
I mean if you're on the monkey app and you're choosing someone else to play roadblocks, don't you come on come on
That's way
Is it though? Is it way different because when you're on monkey app live streaming everybody can see what's going on you're not
Jimmy was doing on a monkey app that I know he was talking to kids
It leads me to believe that you're also trying to talk to kids.
There's that cannoli.
You cannoli.
What's going on, bro?
You know, on Monkey App, it's like the rules
are that you're supposed to be 18 to be honest.
Yeah, but they're not.
None of them are.
None.
It's like an urban, like...
Roblox is the way to get towards the rules.
Weird.
For adults.
I don't know man. I don't know. I don't think I've seen one adult on there besides groovy Jimmy and apparently you. And apparently you.
All these people.
You know what? He doesn't even have a child to count because I think he's like 12 years old because of his like, you know, Mugio.
Mugio is fine. I don't have a problem with Mugio man. That's fine.
I don't know. I don't know.
And I haven't even been in your chat with it. I've assumed him what who else like our G
No, I don't know you
Psychi, why does your why is the title called all are welcome except KZ? What did that little rascal do this time?
Didn't I tell you didn't I tell you about him from day one so he's so annoying
He sets his microphones terrible and then he's annoying and then he went to a lisa giordana's um discord
It said that i said that she was not a good streamer and i was a better
That's what he does and i said just i want to tell you this now
I i said the same thing about j dog and there will be a day
That i say to you remember what i said about j dog
Just like KZ. I promise you. Yeah, he comes in and he says he paid and then he never does and he actually sends me
Um, like requests instead of payments, you know
It's like you just keep sending the request and then like and then he says oh, I don't understand how to do it
And then he's like, oh, let me just warn you about him. You gave me so much shit cuz now he's a good guy
No, he's an I told you this and again
I said the same thing about Jay dog and there will be a day where I get to tell you I told you so
Having said that Janet again, I'm very disappointed. I thought we had an agreement
You know poor grandma love was depended on this agreement, too. You obviously don't care about
I don't want to play with Janet anymore. I want to be
She needs to honor her side of this agreement is what needs to happen
We don't have to be friends, but we could exist in the same space
RG, the PR for you messing with grandma love will not be-
I don't care about PR.
They always mess with grandma love.
We don't have to pay attention this whole time we've done each other.
Come on, psych.
Okay.
It's not, really, it's not Janet now.
I think you and Janet have this kind of like, you know, spool yard crush on each other.
I don't find you attractive.
But maybe it's like some thing I'm not even aware of who knows who knows like a male Janet, but I mean, what do you look like?
No, I'm a adorable
No, no, she calls him a white boy. She called him a white boy. I'm adorable site is actually the truth of it
Tommy
You're a vial or a door. I'm kidding.
Like, let's, let's not be killed here, bro.
Randos adorable because the other bro.
Oh, fuck yeah.
So I said it right away, I'm not a homo.
No offense to the homos here.
Well, you know.
And you sure?
No, honestly, I don't want to, I don't want to fuck with Janet anymore.
Why is she trying to get out of here?
Yeah, because if you, it's like Janet's like, you know,
like sometimes she's going to be like a wild beast.
If you like.
Yeah, I know, but Alex goes after IP two people.
She goes after people who are already openly Docs. Why does she think Alex is gonna fight her back?
Are you calling him from a cafe in Nigeria? Are you a Yahoo boy?
I could be. I could absolutely be Nigerian. You'll never know. You'll never know.
Yeah, I'm telling you
Fucking Arthur is like Puerto Rican or something that would blow my mind. Yeah, he looks like almost like
He was like a
We're good. Yeah
Yeah
He's a brown he's a brown
So yeah, why can't we
I don't I don't I haven't given it that much thought that's why I just said brown
Oh Janet Janet Janet man hasn't even been 48 hours
She's trying to get Alex against me
Well, she has to do it off from the Jimmy and we're everyone's good. Stay away from the sicko. That's all you got to do
That's all you stay away from the sicko
Alexandra is taking or Alexander's taking a 30-day break from the show
Well, I hope she you know, I whatever I don't know. I like yeah, why is that because the warlock dude?
I know you don't think that is yeah, the warlock. I absolutely an energy vampire warlock. I agree. I agree with
But I think that is the devolved guy from Canada, but he was on the he was on
He was fucking Canadians. I'm telling you. I know they call it so much trouble
I told you KZ was a weirdo, and I told you J-Dog is a weirdo.
I'm telling you, this guy got into a VC with a handicap disabled guy
and got him to jerk off on him, dude.
There's gonna be a day where he shows a few colors you see it and I get to tell you I told you so I just like KZ
I told you so
Watch and that goes for Alex and everyone else who who's buying J dogs bullshit
It's all good. It's it's I enjoy J dog because he's so pathetic. He's fun to fuck with
Especially when he thinks he's a tough guy with that
You never asked me to jerk off for a minute
Ask him maybe you got to do it. No, you just want people to
What you wish those rings and shit and he wants to be all manly
But honestly, god if you ask him in a private setting
Like after the stream is done if he's still up and no one's watching he'll 100%
100% do it for you. You'll probably shove things up his ass. So if you ask
Channel versus vod's, um, I think we have that sort of work. Oh, yeah, he was
Yeah, dude, he'll totally jack out for you. You just want people to know now you're good lord of the group
Dude, I'm telling you catch J-Dog after the three men's and he gets to put that
I'm a tough guy with a list personality away, dude
He'll put you'll whip his dick right off and start yeah
He's a hundred percent a gay man. No no question in my mind
Any content creators like bonds don't hide content creators because then it's like
Then they will like, you know create content about everybody you have absolutely no control your chat. I don't think you ever did
My mods like don't stop hiding lures the group because then I'll make a
You know the cartoon my turn to something I like the first ones, right?
But it's like I don't want to like
You know looking worse than I did I need to make one of J dog and you're jacking off back stays together
It's slanderous to all of us everybody
You find Jay dog that grows, huh? Me too. I think he's grow. He's a gross human. I
Let you block. Oh, I let him block the stage. Yeah. Yeah, be careful about blocking members, too
That's where the money comes from psych
Maybe she told Alex she got sent something today that never happened that's a blatant lie
She's blatantly lying to trying to weaponize Alex
During when I was on out on the show, but you pissed off Tony
He's doing all this shit to me so I mean they're doing it for months. I'm gonna read this comment by slay sway slay it says
J-Dog sucks the creepy bastard harasses a woman while he makes believe just sits there like some sad
Invalid special needs person wheelchair ridden and can't speak
I'm reading comments. This isn't my thoughts
I know but I'm saying he's there's a really cheap like little pork swing you sit down. I thought we'll share
I know he's a degenerate and he likes sexualizing low cows and he had a Tony the conductor
There's gonna just like KZ just like you KZ I told you he was no good and the same thing's gonna happen with
So I told you so he's a weirdo creep
There he is. Oh, there he is. Oh, it's a tough guy security protector
Sam you had someone up here trying to throw rope Roblox
Is not it was always just bait to get him on panel
Sam and I thought I told them it wasn't true. I said you're I said
Once again
You said you'd like Roblox, right a dog has masturbated with Tony the black dragon a man a disabled man in a wheelchair
I mean, it's like 500 people seen the Marty stream
500 this is a well-known fact within our whole community. How can you lie about that?
How can jpeg why about that?
They expect people to believe
So the answer your question you probably will jack off with you
So you just got to ask him nicely and make sure no one's around
That's not my true belief on this. I tell you we're on a break Sam and we're on a 30-day break
And I didn't go to her joke. I want to
So I'm taking a dump. She's just we're misunderstanding because she thinks the thing that is is like a tinnity of mastermind
The warlock guy really freaked her out
But I know I think it's a mild manner nice guy
Not nice and like
You know, he's not like
Hey, he seems nice to me. I don't know
So if you do ask a good question if you're disabled, can you consent?
Kid Mason consent
No, there's no dragon, there's nothing they would be
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, it's not a war, you dumbass.
It's a war you're trying to make up.
That's what the fuck you're doing. It's a narrative you're trying to make up. That's
exactly show proof. Show proof show proof you over here trying to slander me everywhere
you fucking go. You ain't gonna do it. You ain't gonna do it. You ain't gonna do it.
You're a piece of shit. You got no proof. You got nothing. You guys should already knows
You haven't heard it come from me, or you ain't seen no proof, don't believe it man, we're not believed motherfuckers, they're going to try to talk shit and say this and that.
You didn't see it come from me, it's not true.
You didn't see it come from me, it ain't true.
It's a hundred percent true.
What are you about?
Here's the thing.
Who the fuck are you there?
You look like a yeah, you're the robots player
He'll be back. I'm not gonna be up here for long. So anyways, I'm gonna turn my bike back down. Hold on
Yeah, everyone in the Cyrus community already knows that J dog jacked off of this dude
He doesn't want people in this community to know and I'm sorry more people know J dog
Don't be a sicko having said that don't stalk fucking women or harass them either
Okay, I think it was bathroom rage. I think we just got some J dog bathroom rage fantastic
My my sound just turned on actually we join. Hello. Can you do me a favor? Oh, you can't say no
I was gonna say say and word a faggot, but
Yeah, I was only kidding
Don't do it again. I said new guy. I say I'm the new guy. I'm the new guy
Are you from the people's podcast? Yeah, that's clear. It's true. I'm gonna make sense
A bunch of winners
Every time I see the people's podcast, I know what I'm getting I know what I'm getting
I know if we're like basing on the homeless and sleeping. I'm not talking about IP team. I barely know those folks
Okay, people podcast. I do know I do know those guys and they just my house fire. Yes, I can do it again
Lay your hair on fire. I don't think you have the ball sir. What was the sound like go up and down after chest
Let me maybe my mic so up alone
No, I let your hair on fire put on a show
They got a lot of curly hairs down in fucking Denmark a little Jew in you you got a little Jew in you, sir
You know now my mic is better, but like my I see it's not so bad
Not gonna interact at all. It's gonna
Days into the camera like that you weirdo. Are you here on fire? It was your idea. I
Can do whatever boy. I'm I'm much better content than you. I don't everything
I'm gonna we I cannot almost hear you boy. I'm gonna we join again. Okay, when you come back and then yeah
I'm done have fun psych Janet. I'm disappointed in you. I'm disappointed in you
You man, what are you problem dude? You sound so angry? It doesn't work for that accent
Get a fucking lot of look my girlfriend. Stop right now
I'm gonna talk to a real woman without you with this blunt bitch
You don't got nobody. Yeah, man. Here's rando
Can I see it? Can I see what's hits? Yeah
Oh
That's a good says man
Sorry, dude, I had to take a phone call. I apologize for that. I know
Well, you're kind of like, you know, I'm trying to show the dip this a Danish got my kids
I mean, you don't have to have me on a screen like you school full screen your tits. I don't give a fuck
I want to fuck this woman
So real quick psych I wanted to like offer your proposition so I know that you like this AI
Some people ain't the best at like visual stuff like but and some people ain't the best like audio
Yeah, but you can't just go in AI videos without being good at one thing like pick picking shoes like
You know, don't you don't have to be an audio guy so you could do your like own vid
Like a video editing, but when you just do both it's kind of like this
Let the woman be man, yeah
How are you doing? I think you are buddy hand or buddy
Yes, I will fuck you so hard man. You're crazy. I love I love to dominate another man in the ass
It's the worst thing you can do to a man. Fuck him and ass
You never done enough coke if you haven't been with a transsexual or a lady boy
Yeah, I've been to Thailand many times you have to try it. It's very good
Like the Asian ones or like I don't know one maybe two but like
Dominating another man the ass is the best thing you can do for yourself
You know like that's real man power, you know, fuck another guy in the ass. Holy shit
You have not done you have not done enough coke if you have never tried it. You have to just do a lot keep do
And then in the end
Yeah, oh shit
Okay, I mean that I think that was just
Okay, I'll be there keep buying a plane ticket
You have another listen, I have a menu worms and very nice I can show you you can come here
Look here. This is my one
Guys
Why does it have locks everywhere?
Is there anybody locked in a room over there?
Oh my god, you're checking the floor. Turn it off. Turn it off.
What?
You see a spider sign. The boat? You don't have a boat?
Oh nice, I have wine here for the wine.
Is there wine cellar?
Yeah, it's just at the beach.
Where are you going to fuck me at?
Out here.
What are you throwing me up over the balcony afterward? Oh, is it in the boat? Are you throwing me overboard?
See oh absolutely
Yeah, I have a jacuzzi also in the garden jacuzzi
Just out here, but it's so dark. I cannot show you
Jacuzzi with me, huh?
You'd like to take a naked jacuzzi with me and then what the fuck was all I have to prove my charge chain again
I think
Fucking go out the sound. It's funny. I just got this phone and it's like iPhone
And when I don't charge it sound go down
It's going down. I want to go down on you. I can almost not hear you man. Can I read you on okay?
No, oh my gosh, he left.
OK.
He'll rejoin.
Yeah, I swear, this wig is paying off.
He's already this really cute guy from Denmark who's
invited me out there.
Looks pretty safe.
It looks like he has a kind of dungeon layout in his house.
Interesting.
Hello?
Yeah, it's better now
Yeah, so I was just saying like um
You're really cute. Thank you very much. You are body cute too. Thank you. I would love to suck your dick
Very hell yes, I have how much yes, too
A little bit. It's starting growing like my beard
No, no
Are you tarot cards? Oh, yeah, yeah, it's probably satanic. Don't do that on me. I'm a Christian
Okay, well, I mean, you know, I don't believe okay, you know
Can I do a?
Hero blowjob, no, no, let me do a tarot. Just
What?
Yes, yes, so yes, you're going to have sex for sure, right? I can do a cocaine
Oh yeah careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful careful care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care care
You know
Maybe you can do a threesome
She can sit in your face, and I will fuck you dude
Okay, I would take it easy
I'll try
Looks like you're not muted, but I'm not sure why I can't
maybe an exit come back I'm not sure yeah well but what's guys what's why is the
chat going nuts you know this is finally I'm yeah finally I'm gonna you know I
have somebody that interested I mean it's this guy but it's still he's pretty cute
really fun
Yeah
What should my name be? Oh my god, that's I don't like that one. I don't like that one. I like that makes your lips look weird
your name should be a
sweet
Sweet blonde sweet blonde dream you like the dream of the sweet blonde, you know, you know
How big is your cock?
I'm very tall, you know two meter
but skinny but my dick oh my god it's like this actually it hits from there to there so it's like
i don't know like 70 no that's two i don't even know but it's very big like you know this can
two of these cans i think almost like two of these beer cans too yeah i think it's very very very
I always get told it's so big. It's too big. The they actually don't like it
He says too much. It hurts. You say it hurt. I can touch the bottom of that pussy in the end
It's crazy
so
But you'd like to kiss you they have you ever just been with one of your put in your male friends
Just been with them a guy just like without they having a trick being a tranny. I mean, what if I forget the wig?
I just like them as a guy can I remember
When I do lines that cannot remember man, so yeah, okay
I'll remember to bring it though, but I just don't want to take it all the way
Okay, it's okay. I can buy another one on team
Okay, I'm good. I mean I will I will uh look forward to that
Fuck forward to what you can come here. I'm gonna fuck you up, dude
No, I'm gonna fuck you fuck you like I seen worse transsexual you can you can go maybe
Much worse. Yeah, probably old old guys with wet hair. Oh
Fuck them. Yes, and I'm a giver. I'm not a taker. I'm not gay. I just fuck Amanda
That's what you dominate. I'm a psyche psychic, you know, like you so just psyched them
I say, oh, oh, oh, you know until they say, oh, stop, stop, stop. It hurts too much
I'm gonna fuck you up, dude. I'm the shit your dog shit. Okay. Yeah
You want to play stupid games, I'll make you with target. Okay in your asshole
I don't know if I want all this because you're like nice. I keep thinking like oh, we're not sex
And then it sounds like you're here. You're gonna beat me to death
Oh, no, are you crazy man?
I have so much work to do tomorrow. I'm gonna do the worst of my coke
But it's so dumb, you know
I talk to a Spanish girl right now, but she's going, she's a nurse, she's fucking hard.
I just started dating her.
But she's going to work, but I have to work some more and shit, but I'm gonna get fucking late.
It's okay, you can enjoy your conversation.
Okay, okay.
No, we want to talk to you.
I'm sorry, I'll give you a minute.
We want to talk to you.
Hey, he's kind of scares me a little bit, but at the same time it's kind of...
Oh, don't be scared.
Great.
You know, because he's saying I'm gonna fuck you up and he's like,
I'm gonna make you retarded and stuff.
I'm like, well, in a good way or a bad way?
Probably in a good way maybe kind of like you know if you have some sort of black guy
You're gonna need a wheelchair. Maybe that's what he means. I yeah, yeah, yeah, that's what I mean
I'm pretty sure Denmark Andy comes from
From them like from Portland Andy era and chicken Andy era
Chicken is my friend the Portland. I never talked to him, but yeah
So he's he's an OG I
Fairly recognize the name. It's cool. It's cool. Yeah, I'm OG. Yeah, but I'm not a OG like that. I was not
Really good old times, but I started coming on the network 2020 so I'm kind of like old school like almost
Five years I've been in in the soup, you know, but I was I was looking at the soup for a lot of years, too
But only stream for like three years, and then I got a will job
this is not
Good shit, you know, but
Yeah, so
You don't this guy look fucking disgusting. I really he really scarce
You're transsexual man, you're fucking disgusting man. You really think I want to fuck somebody or what in there?
I mean, I get busy all the time. I'm a big baller, bro. I just
You're fucking
Yeah, so, yeah, Alexander did purchase you a reading, so I saw like a little bit, I don't know if you wanted a specific, on a specific thing and, you know, a specific topic or something, but I'm shuffling and so.
Did you see why she donated it?
Well, um.
Can you can you just give me a little background and so she feels like that well my understanding of what she was saying
Was that she feels like that I don't really?
Listen to people that give me good advice or that try to steer me in the right direction
And so I'm thinking that maybe she thinks you're gonna give me like a deeper type type of reading to like
Help me steer from my
My bad path, but the thing with Alexandra's. I'm sorry. I heard that I said her name right. It's Alexandra
she
See, I don't think she realized where my life has been going and I don't think she realizes that I don't spend very much
time on the internet and around the internet anymore like I
There's people that give me shit thinking that I don't like care about them anymore, which I still do. It's just
My life has been focusing, I don't even think she realizes I have a job and I have been paying so much more attention to my child and my family, but she wants you to give me a reading, I think that's going to help steer me in the right direction.
is you know because I know you did there's like a maybe a website or
something and it's like maybe it's like not most flat like you know it's like
stuff that kid like people would be really mad at each other about and it's
like I think that you know you're not even like mad or really or I don't know
that's why I saw her maybe warming up to a little bit or like I like that I like
oh me and me and her will never be on good terms she has done a lot of fucked
But it seems like you're mature about it like a little bit like like before like you know
It's like you know even to accept the reading
Well, yeah, I mean I appreciate it and I'll definitely take the reading because
Obviously, I do want to better my life and that's that's how everybody should be and so you know
If there's anything anybody could do that can help of course. I'll listen
So I
Like a little bit like I know
recovery and you know have been trying to turn your life around and or have you
know which I've made a lot of things like I hear a lot of good things and so
But that's where the front-coming part of the slide basically knows, so I'm not sure about any other questions you might have to all do with general.
Yeah, just a general, but let me address easy cameras real quick. Easy cameras, don't worry. This won't take very long.
And the only reason why he's doing it now for me is because I have a crazy schedule and this is like the only chance I have to get this reading.
If not, it'd be like crazy hours in the middle of the night.
And so he's just doing it now for me because I can't, I don't have a whole lot of free time.
But he does want drama, so it's not going to take very long, I promise.
Well, you know, I don't like when people fight and I don't like, but sometimes we have to go through some conflicts to get to this conflict.
Well, that's what people like. They like the drama, and that's what's up with it.
I know, I know. It's hard now to see myself like, oh, you know, it's like, can we just all get along?
Of course, that would be very interesting.
Okay, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 40, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41, 41
Reading for me. So and then you guys can get back to the fuck shit
Okay, so this is some okay, so we have first the knight of swords
Okay, so the knights are this like kind of like more they're not they're not quite the kings yet
They're like basically the kings henchmen so they're out here. They can have some kind of importance and this guy was like
executioner or something
this was
so in the past this person this guy comes over to he's probably really good communicator and
It looks like something about like you're happy
The ten of cups and this is also like
You do have the happiness like where you
You're on your way to some kind of happiness. There's some kind of like really like harmony has been happening
Actually, like that's like the happily ever after card it's like it's like it's kind of quick once you get to the tag house
It's just like kind of
Oh
Okay, are you there? Okay. I'm sorry. I'm here. I just I just muted it because you're gonna hear probably my kiddo in
the background in the living room, and I'm just trying to avoid that.
Okay, we have, okay, we have, we have a death and the judgment card coming up.
Okay, so I consider this like top row like like basically with like a foundational or it's like, you know,
recent past, so I don't know if there was like some kind of death and from the death a judgment was called.
Okay.
but I'm not sure what this is actually referring to.
Wait, can you explain that one a little bit more?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, so the death card can't mean
like an actual physical death.
Like someone, somebody passing away,
because I think this is in the past.
This would be more of the recent past.
And also, but also there's a judgment card
and so I see that this, that.
Either the death or the end of the relationship or whatever something ended, right?
It had to be an ending whatever it was like
It was like there was some kind of judgment call because something was not right in it
like something was not fair or and so
And I don't know so I don't know if they did that was some more in a jail or something like that or know someone
I do know someone who recently passed and it was all it was very sudden death. Okay. Yeah
It looks like it's like
To the judgment
Which is like, you know, the setting where they'll go and stuff like that, right, um.
It does, okay, so that was our first row, okay, that's a more recent pass.
So in the present time, we have, okay, we have nine of cups.
That means that like, I think you've been like doing a lot of like resting,
relaxation, more taking care of yourself.
spending a good quality alone time and like finding happiness in that because
the nine is also like you know associated with the Hermit card which is
like number nine but so this is like basically you've been in a good state of
mind I think you're in a good state of mind and also you're in this kind of
battle right now okay and this battle will
I see you do, I see you winning this battle because it's like, okay, so there's a battle and this is like
Actually, you against like a lot of other people
It's also all these towns people and it's like and then the spring inside is like but who's the monsters like the crowd or it's like the monster, right?
but
So I feel like you're you are in this battle or at least on a strong defense a strong defense right now
But then I see like you do have this big three coming like you're gonna win
But it's could be the kind of like a brutal kind of winning like you know, it's like kind of like
It's like in the swords competitions, they're kind of like, you know, there's the winners and there's the losers and it's like, it's not like a friendly competition, it's like a strong strong thing.
Okay, well also we have, okay, so heartbreak over some, like a heartbreak and then I see like it was over somebody that passed away, because you have the three or three of swords and it's like, but then it's like she's got the skull, she's got that memory.
That's the page of pinnacles.
Yeah, it definitely hit me pretty good.
I mean, it's not like,
I wasn't like super, super, super close to them,
but I just, it was somebody that
helped me a lot and had been there a lot.
And then it was just all of a sudden.
Yeah, super good.
And it says, but also it's like,
I see like the heartbreak and it's like,
but also like, there's something that it's like,
can be provided to you,
either something you've learned or something that it's like,
It's just there's some kind of material manifestation of like something that it's actually
Going to turn out for you. Also, like the ace of sorts. So this is like the truth card. I'm going to go to another deck after this
Okay, so then so
You're either learn the truth about something or you're learning the truth
But and you've heard the truth about something or you know the truth about something, okay?
That's like the really important thing coming up in the future is that you know this truth
Oops, it's popped out right away.
Okay, okay, what is this?
This is an enticement.
Okay, so beware of like,
and it's like this enticement is like,
see it's like this kind of like a little nerdy
like a lawyer kind of looking guy.
So it could be like something like,
but he's like trying to tempt her or something, right?
And oh yeah, and then she's being distracted
by this guy behind her with a spider, okay?
So it's like, don't be distracted.
And it's like, even if something seems boring
or something like that,
these like people in suits or whatever because there's like somebody trying to distract you or
like say you don't understand something or you've missed something okay they're trying
well that could be with me getting off drug court soon and
You know it's everything's gonna be in my control as far as sobriety and stuff like that
So I think that's a little like a really like a lawyer feeling from the sky, too
Like it's like, you know lawyers are gonna be really boring. I just say like listen to the lawyer
He's trying to explain something important like so I don't know
And then we have, this one is a ephemera, okay?
Okay, this is like, ephemera is like all these little things.
It's like, I mean, this is about just enjoying the moment
as it goes and like enjoying,
like taking the scenic route of cards,
letting yourself be, maybe driven or like letting yourself be,
you know, taking care of like, you know,
sitting in the back of a car rather than having to drive
everywhere, right?
I like that.
That does kind of feel like what's been going on lately.
I have just been, I just been just going slow
and just enjoying.
It's in the back too.
Yeah, she's in the back like doing stuff in the car
while she's on her way, okay?
And then,
We also have convergence.
Okay, so I know this is like a really a portal card.
This is like coming into like a new reality.
I don't know if you felt this recently.
I feel like we are October 10th and 11th.
I think those are big days.
And that kind of looks like an 11 too.
But I think-
If I felt what?
They're big days.
It's like an energy shift.
Like a portal opening almost into like a new reality
for some people, right?
Whenever portals happen,
I think there's an opportunity for ascension.
And it's like all these all these things came together at once and like allowed you to like make a choice of which door to go through
They all came together and it's like the
It was it was the kind of a easier decision to make because they're all there. Okay. We also have the stranger. Okay
This is like help from an unexpected
Person or somebody that might be considered, you know weird looking or strange
It's only that they all but they might be very like smart about something and like the strangers like
look at like he's telling her about something about the time or like time travel or something
like that.
Sometimes I just get these things printed in my head like I didn't see different details
when I look at the cards and we also have oh the affair okay so and then so I don't
know if this is like a you know just an affair like oh you know just a relationship with
an older guy or something like that or it's actual affair or something like that but
or maybe he's having the affair, I'm not sure,
but or maybe something that you'll come into knowledge about
or somebody, because they look like they're kind of cocky,
cock about something, okay, two more from this one.
Okay, this one says the staircase.
Okay, some kind of ascension for you,
like coming into a higher place, continuing to evolve.
And a new level I got I got that with the portal and this too
And it might be something with this like love or like sex sex that helps you get up there
And finally we did this one says departure. Okay, whatever that
That's there. It might be like leaving you leaving things behind
Okay, or it might be like leaving that person behind but it's like it is kind of a grim reaper kind of energy
To that's the second one. I got isn't it departure. Yeah, well, it's like
We have enticement, ephemera, the staircase is similar, and the convergence, the convergence was similar.
And so, but also, yeah, also it could be like a fear too.
It kind of reminds me a little bit of this guy.
Oh, there you go. That guy and the groom is really good.
Because I'm definitely not having an affair and I doubt Sarge is, you know.
Well, an affair could mean just like...
My old man is old.
Okay. He's old, okay.
We have pursuit, okay.
And so running after something, in this case it's like some kind of wish.
It's like it's like closed and it might be further away because it's a star, you know,
Don't get too pulled off track by them because it's like again with the entitlement like something taking away from what you're supposed to be paying attention to
I'm gonna put one more from this deck. This one says
Salvation okay, and it's like I think she's like I think she's at the church or something like that
And there's a big monster and she's like welcoming this monster or something like that or trying to save
Save him or maybe save somebody that people were like oh that don't save that person
I just get this like energy of like
People they look like a lot of judgment around of people like, you know, it's kind of like monstrous people that maybe is like unfair, okay?
It's gonna pull through from this and there and then
Give me other questions
Okay, so this one says
Red does forgive. Okay, and this is also she's taking a bath. Okay. I say like you're taking a good spiritual bath
Maybe involving salt coffee, lemon. That's why I like that of mine. Those are really good ways to get
Negative energy off of you, but also it's like this forgiveness energy. It says red
And she had at least like roses and stuff in the bath though.
But it's something you need to be forgiving about something
and maybe forgiving yourself.
And so when you take that spiritual bath,
like release all that resentment or anything
you have towards anything.
Okay.
We also have feather.
And it's a bunch of people gathered around
and it said, I didn't turn my light real quick, I'm sorry.
Okay, so feather says.
This one says, think before you judge.
Think first before you judge, okay?
And so maybe there's something you don't believe
or like some kind of like,
oh, we can do this, we can do this.
And you're like, I don't know about that,
but it's like, you know,
it's like thinking about something,
thinking first, because it's like,
there are miracles possible.
There's like other people like that,
like, you know, the power of three and stuff.
And then this one says, storm.
It says, every hurricane.
comes to an end. Okay. And so it's like, you might have been like, you've been holding onto your crown and stuff like that. You might have been through like the storm and everything. But it's like, you know, you're able to like weather it. And it's like, and then the storm will find the end. And it's calm and peaceful. Right. And so it's like, you'll get through it, no matter how like, crazy it may seem sometimes.
You know, okay, and then I'll pull.
We're from this deck and then
Take any question if you want this one you got the this one says the cold shoulder
Maybe being either receiving the cold shoulder or you've been giving the cold shoulder or somebody
and it's like
Get the feeling that it's like it's like someone feels like that you are to then like you're
Unaccessible, but that might be for a good reason. Okay?
The zoom meeting and it's like kind of like that meme where it's like everything's fine
And like things are on fire or something like that
But it's like but it is like she's just on the computer, right? It's like shit
But it's like yeah, she remember she remember like not to be too distracted
Do things like that like I got you know, it's like there's stuff on the other and the outside world going on too
Like that you should be paying attention sometimes, right?
And then
We have the last hurrah, and so it's like maybe like we have one more time of doing something or like you're
Closing out some cycle and so it's like you're finishing it like up with the with the boom or something like that
But I've been doing one thing about something for a final time. It's like, you know
In a positive way kind of yeah, I was gonna say I hope it's not
Like relapsing anything because
Because that's like the I feel like a lot of the departure and the ascension and
All of that has to do with literally me actually being ready to change for the first time in my life and not
Just do what I have to do and go back to my old ways. So, um
Yeah, because it looks like it just does look like another card because the other one was like the departure card, right?
This one is also like a departure from like these rough waters like in the past.
It's always like a nice thing. So like kind of like an end to like a lot of
conflicts. It seems like there's like
the one with the storm shoe, it's like these things are like
Becoming peaceful and just take advantage of the peaceful times, you know
Because you can get a lot done during them and there's like a lot of distractions to get some stuff that you want to get done
And so and then make sure
You're paying attention to everything you should be in this war like it's like yeah
I feel like like the people are talking to you like lawyers or business or things like that
Okay, I saw that and also like well, you know, it's crazy about the lawyer thing is I'm going to school to be legal assistant
Yeah, and I feel like that part where you were talking about the the wish or the thing that I'm going after when you're talking about the star
Like I feel like that's what that is is that finishing my schooling and not because I am a felon
And I do have to get it expunged and that could be a hindrance
And so I feel like that's was enough don't give up like don't be don't be like a stray like right also like I think
That there are like any hindrance like yeah, it could be like you know on the mainstream level it could be like a more typical
But also, I think, like, you know, they will maybe bring you across somebody that maybe, like, you know,
have experienced the same thing in the past or something. There's like, sometimes there are people that could help you.
you know exactly yep and there's people that I work with that that have
experience in that field and so I'm looking forward to that and the zoom
meeting thing that hit home because like I feel like everyone I'm trying to do my
homework my son's always like smacking my computer knocking out of my hands and
I'm like trying to focus on my schoolwork and like so I feel like that was
referring to that right and then we got the true card too is like it's like
really I see that like you're just coming to like understandings of the truth
Or like maybe they thought we're true or not true and then you've seen the truth and so now it's and so now it's like more of like you know the truth and then you can use that like a sword like cut through like the illusion of the world or powers now with that so I hope you like that.
No, I did like that reading. I appreciate that a lot. Thank you.
Problem.
It just tells me to keep going so.
Yeah, keep going. I would say definitely and it's like, but it's like I see.
It's just very positive and it's like with the staircase and everything too, it's like
I see like a lot of progression, like a lot of like, like leaving the dead, you know,
get like the dead kind of like behind him buried and you know, like moving on from like all that
it's like because you've probably been through like storms, right? You've been through like a big storm.
I mean some storms, there's you know, given where I'm working now, I've really come to see how
good my life was and is and always has been, you know, what I mean? Like, there's like, I mean, I've always had a mentality of like, there's always someone or someone out there who's at worst, but I'm like finding people that like 1920 that have just experienced so much bad and and it's just like, you know, just makes me be even more grateful and humble and helpful and appreciative for what I do have.
I think a part of that departure thing is too,
is like all the internet stuff,
like the internet was a big part of my life
when I was on drugs,
like a big part of my life
and I've just tried to step away
and it's still its own addiction.
That's why I still pop in every once in a while
and try and like catch up to the drama,
but as far as like choosing sides
and hating on other people,
because of other,
like I'm not, it's not me and I'm just.
Right.
And that is a big transformation too,
is like how you interact online.
You know stoke flames and like for all of that shit or like, you know, you're there
It's like you just observe and like maybe like be a positive positive influence and like, you know
You will make people will make good friends and things like that and it's also it's good to I think you have ability to help
because I think you have been maybe maybe wounded but um like it like instead of like
Continuing like negative cycles you're like a cycle breaker and so you're you're able to break negative cycles and then also
That would include like the cycles of like repeating what would happen to people, you know
And so I think that you could be more of the wounded healer energy where it's like you've been through it
So you know how and that's and I appreciate that because it's kind of what I am trying to do
It's like I try to tell because people are still doing the oh you did this you did this
No, we've all done fucked up shit and it's just a matter of how we how we go forward and like
Here's Kate, Kate and Sage are trying to trigger me and chat and it's not going to work because I it's just hella old news in the past and it just doesn't get the reaction out of me anymore that it would like.
There's a really good quote and that quote is every saint has a past and every sinner has a future and so.
I like that.
You know, they came through things not very, you know, a lot of crazy things.
We have to experience bad, I think, to understand the good, like, you know, like, you don't need to sleep without the sour, like, the yin and the yang.
Like, I understand that a lot. Like, it takes, you have to experience something to be able to understand both sides. I really feel.
Right, that's why a lot of people don't really like learn because the teachers, a lot of the teachers in America are not in their career, they're teaching their career, and so they don't have the real-hold experience about it.
They have a different understanding of it, but it's not very applicable. They just learn.
Like certain knowledge, knowledge is not very useful, it's like you don't know what to do with it, right?
So people can know a lot of stuff and not be able to make things happen in the world.
But I see that you are able to manifest things.
So be very careful with like...
What you do focus on because it's like, you know, you are creating your reality. Like maybe like
I know you're I don't mean air sign
air sign in your chart or something air in your chart where it's like
Taking the ideas and taking them into like
Manifestation I can be powerful with that. And so just realize that the power of your own thoughts and power of
Your communication and you're much more powerful than you think too. And so it's like also give the power to like
You know the people up or you know to maybe hurt people and so it's like you know
You should make sure you use your power for good and like you know and I agree with that
I appreciate that a lot actually. Thank you. The problem. I tried to like fix age, you know, you look really good in those nerdy
Preppy
Turtle necks that you wear
You know and Kate you're hilarious, but they both still suck
I do like to lift people up and that's the thing and that's where I tell people like
The way I was before like like on the internet all that hate and shit like that wasn't me and and you know
It's also like contagious and it's like and it goes really into like that the group mind kind of like that's how the
Bullying always like takes on this like life of its own with the group, right? Oh, there's
No, it's funny.
No, and I understand, so I get it.
So I just try to be better and do better.
Remember, especially in these communities,
you're going to be trying to be triggered.
And they're going to have some of your triggers,
because we all reveal some more triggers along the way.
And it's impossible not to get.
Oh, definitely.
There's still a few that trigger me.
Right.
And so you just have to be even more aware of your triggers
that you do have.
You know also, I always say like patrol something like it's a exposure training. It's like basically you go through the worst of it
That's like it's not really a big deal anymore because you're like mentally prepared or mentally, you know fortified
with anything so no one can really say anything that will ever bother you because you've already
been called the worst accused of the worst and you know and yeah exactly it's all been said done
heard shared experience there's not much more somebody heard me and that's also powerful because
it's logical that lacks the experience of things and it's like it's just so
and also people that could learn from your experiences and so
you know and you as well just make sure to keep learning from people because
it's like we're always like learning. Exactly, exactly.
I am not born you know Arthur like you were mean to me and then when you saw
Cleavage you were nice to me and now you're mean to me again because
apparently it's been a while since you've seen Cleavage so you need to chill out.
Arthur is like Arthur are you bipolar? I mean, it's like he's like you he loves me one day
Yes, Arthur is hella bipolar
He so Arthur is one of those people that can't like come up with his own personality has to imitate other people's personalities
So he's he's trying everyone else is like little sticks and then seeing what works for him and nothing works for him
That way he's talking like elders the other day
Yes, probably.
All those coppings, Sandman's personality, and so who's, who's, who's the original personality
you're on?
I don't know what I'm saying, it's hard to find out.
I've never, I've never been married Joe 2.0, so there's no ex-husband that could have
ran for the hills.
Oh.
Come on Arthur come up. You wanted to leave come up Arthur. I think someone's in the background
Don't ever say anything about psyches AI he'll just boot you out the panel
It's crazy
Okay, okay, I retry I'm sorry whatever but Amber Amber
I don't know like I don't know who you are anything but uh, I don't think the whole recovery thing has anything to do with like
Online behavior has nothing to do with it
No, I wasn't in recovery.
Oh, you figured it's not.
I am now. Like, I was on drugs and did things that weren't me. Like, I didn't.
I didn't have a care in the world. I didn't give a fuck right
But what I'm saying is that has nothing to like getting high has nothing to do with how you act online
Getting high on drugs has a lot to do with how you act and a lot of people do things that are
Against their own morals and their own principles. I'm not saying it's 100% the reason like obviously I had it in me to do it
but
it definitely
Helps me avoid thinking about consequences or any or hurting anybody or anything like that lack of inhibitions. So is that how bad?
It's so it got so bad for you that you were um
What fighting with people online? Is that really it was more than just fighting? Okay?
It went like real shit. Oh
Okay, I don't know anything about I'm new. I'm sorry
No, it's fine like but and I did fucked up shit said fucked up shit. That's what I'm saying
None of us none of us are innocent
It's like but I know that I did things that weren't me and that thinking back now
Discussed me that they did delete back page. That was back when I was like that was back in my day, you know, the
No, no, no the women. Yeah, the women they would definitely be on back page
You don't oh, okay. That page is like basically it's like Craigslist of prostitution. That's like where yeah, it was a craigslist of prostitution
Is that what you did? No, okay
No
You ain't done yet. It sounds like you ain't done yet. Why do you say that?
You don't even know what we're talking about
But what do you mean? I'm not done yet
It doesn't sound like it got bad enough for you well
That's why I mentioned earlier that obviously there are people that have gotten things done to them that were far worse than what happened to me like
But what do you mean? I'm not done yet just because I'm here right now. Yes. I didn't say I was completely done
So what are you using you on suboxone or what? No, no, I'm completely done with this rug. Just just
It's okay random guy just wants to come up here and he's trying to to prove some point but
Clean you're not clean if you're on suboxone. I said it. I said it. I agree with that
Like certain drugs that people like can do and that people can't do it's like there's like a couple of chemistry, right?
Is there certain ones that are going to be pretty much bad?
No, so let me clarify a little bit more, random guy.
What I mean is, in my sober mind,
there's certain ways that I choose and feel like I should
react to certain, yes, maybe I'm going to eat it.
And it was, yes, there's ways that I
react to certain situations that I reacted to or would
So like I and then like I said the internet. Thank you, babe
The internet is still its own addiction and so obviously I still want to show my face and see what's going on with people
But I don't get myself as involved as I did before with the battles and the hurting people the tearing people down and
I just I've my priorities have changed. I guess I should say people that you are you sure? I don't know if you're trans you trans
I don't know. I just I am not gonna ask you. Nope. Not trans
Why would that matter?
It wouldn't I'm just wondering. I just like to know the characters. That's it. Oh, yeah. No, no, this is not a character
This is actually me
I
Came out with a bird
Yeah, I'm slow
No, but honestly if you want to be real if you want to be real you're talking about like what were you doing?
What kind of drugs are we doing?
Doesn't count but it does it does but you're talking about like smoking meth and getting off meth and like
Comparing like saying how bad it got and you're saying that you're trolling people online
It just makes like a real addicts think like what are you you fucking serious?
No, I am like I've done it for someone. No, I'm not saying that the only part of my life that was
Yeah
Yeah, why don't you talk about like scratching your fucking face off like talk about the real shit?
No, oh, I was acting all crazy online like what?
I we were talking about online things, but no my life got really bad on drugs. That's a whole like I
Mean most of my life was is already aired on the internet my body camp but it's just up there for my arrest like I've not ever been like
I'm a very transparent person
So I guess you are new because you would understand absolutely am I a part of the downfall because it was all it's all been online
It's all my whole everything in my personal life has been aired online. So it's not like I'm
So I guess when I say the internet that includes like by shit that was happening in real life
Like I'm not so you're like live streaming your whole act of addiction
Well, not to the extent of me using online. No
You may as well though, right? I might as well. Have you
That's wild
Where can we work and I see that at?
What the body cam footage? I don't know if it's still up. No, just like you said, okay
So you like you hopped on stream high a lot, right? Mm-hmm
Let's see, um
Pull it up
most of my streams from
Prior to
May of last year I was on drugs
What's your what's your channel called? Yeah, let's see this shit. You look up a wrench
At sign a wrench, you'll find it easier than trying to find amber it was for ages
Yeah, that's crazy because back back of my day
I don't know like we would avoid even like posting on Facebook as we were like embarrassed of how we looked when we were getting
I well, I mean you're talking about you just live stream the whole fucking thing crazy
Crazy, absolutely crazy. Do you think that I'm lying about being in recovery? No, no, no
I'm just saying like people the people that I knew they kind of like
Didn't go on so many when they're getting hot. They knew how fucked up they were and they're like, yeah, fuck this
Well, that's no like I that's where again. I was talking about earlier how I never had it bad as a lot of people like I've never been homeless
I've never been sexually assaulted. I've never been held by gunpoint for anything. I've never been robbed
I oh you ain't done yet
You ain't done yet
Oh, i'm done. I'm no, you know, I am I don't it didn't get bad it didn't get bad enough for you
I don't everyone's rock bottom is different. I don't have to experience all that stuff to learn how
It has affected my life and to be over it like I don't have to experience that I can learn from other people's lessons
yeah
I'm grateful for the fact that I didn't have to experience all that sounds good on paper Amber, but I don't believe it
Well, you know, that's what recovery is like. I don't know if you heard the part of my reading where I mentioned
I'm just trying to help you out. I
Don't I don't think by trying to
not encouraged a future of sobriety is helping me out. I understand that you think you're being realistic
But I don't think you understand that not everybody has to experience like complete hardship
That's what they say, but that's not how it usually plays out. Well, I hope I hope it never to that point me too
I hope you're saying yes
You guys have experienced recovery rando. That's maybe why you're yes, sir
You're still in recovery. You're always in recovery.
13 years.
Oh, wow.
And what was the worst point of your addiction?
I mean, shoving a needle in your arm is pretty bad, right?
I mean, yeah, I've never done that.
Yet.
See?
I'm not going to.
Even in my, even in the worst part of my addiction.
See, that's what we were talking about.
When you start thinking you're above something, that's, listen,
you're in a bad spot.
I don't think I'm above it.
You're in a bad spot.
I knew I was above it in my addiction. That was one thing I would never do because I know I would really listen
I'm gonna quit preaching this ain't the place for it. I just you know, I wish you the best
But I know a bullshitter when I hear one
How what am I bullshitting there's just a bullshitter what am I bullshitting though?
That I don't want to be clean everything you say so you think that even though I want to be clean
I'm not going to be I just know your mindset Amber. I've seen thousands of people like you. I know your mindset
So rather than just go to a meeting. Okay. I go to meetings every week. I go to meetings like every other day
I work for I work. Yes. I have a sponsor and a mentor. I work full fucking time
I go to a female sponsor ladies. No, I work in recovery. No, I don't like I said, I don't know who fuck you are
Exactly, so I so you got a job at like a rehab or a group home or something like that
But yes, I am see I knew your type boom
I'm just spinning it out, but I want to be clean and surrounded
So just because I didn't experience needles and being rape doesn't mean that I don't want to not you can't say on the screen
That's that's violation
Sorry, sorry
But just because I didn't experience all that doesn't mean that I don't want to be clean
Doesn't mean I don't you said you were above some you said you were above something. That's a red
I say I was above it. I said I've never done that. Do you put words in my mouth? No, I didn't you did
I never once said I'm above
shooting needles
I'm a drug addict
No, better than any other drug addict. I just said I've never done that and you know why I never did it
I didn't do needles because I know my personality
I'm a very addictive personality and I know that I would have liked it and loved it and things would just have gotten worse like I
Just think you're being really argumentative right now
No, are you I think you're not
That's your opinion
You're calling me a boat
So if you're in recovery the last thing you should do is like feel like you're steering someone into the past of you
No, I'm telling you about yourself. I'm busting your ass. That's what we call it. You're getting your ass busted. And that's okay
That's okay, but I still don't think you should be calling someone a bullshit or he was only
So you're one of those easier and softer types, right? No, you know everything
No, did I say I know everything? I know me better than you. Oh my god. This is so difficult. I'm
It's easier in real life. Okay. I didn't listen you gotta stick with the ladies
I don't know what the ladies
I don't know what that even means. I don't listen
I'm surrounded by some of the most hardest fucking NA people who like run the conventions and shit like that
Don't think that I haven't been talked down to and talked to like how I should be but not once did they tell me
Oh, you're not done yet. You're gonna go use again
You need to you need to experience you're hanging around with the wrong people that amber you need don't you need to experience
You're easier and softer you you need to go get graped and go shoot needles before you
Did that really happen to you?
I'm not done yet. You're telling me I'm not done yet, but if you're telling me that I have to go experience those things before I'm done
No, I know I don't I don't want to I don't need to I don't have to
But that's the only way that I'm gonna be able to be fully in recovery is by experiencing those things before I
I'm fully in recovery. That makes no fucking sense. Well, you must have been the best addict ever
You never got ripped off for meth one time. Yep had all the perfect connects never got ripped off
I got ripped off hell, yeah
Oh, no, we're doing semantics now. That's pretty much get it wrong
I mean, I feel like he thinks I'm like glorifying my drug use and I'm not kind of worry Amber
Like she's always been um as far as I've known her. She's always been like
And talking my recovery and helping people as far as I've seen so
And that's been for quite a while.
That's what I'm saying, not everyone has the same low point.
Not everyone has to experience all that to know that they don't.
The drugs, I mean, drugs have been bad or bad.
They've done a lot of fuck.
I mean, they've ruined a lot of good things in my life.
But I don't need to experience those kind of hardships to know that I'm done. I'm ready for the change
I'm ready to be better for my family. I'm ready to be better. You don't understand
I popped in I popped in the panel hearing you talk about oh my god
So bad with my drug use that I was you know fighting with people online, and I came in like what?
Okay, I understand that I understand where you're coming from what I meant was I
Didn't mean that just month the internet part of my life got affected what I meant was
While during my internet time while I was on drugs
It didn't make my actions online. Like they weren't me. I
Guess I was we were talking about internet that we were talking about the internet at that
I don't even think you should have been online if you're fucking getting high like what well
I was lying to everybody. I was pretending like I wasn't on drugs. I was trying to do what I thought normal people would be doing
while
You know, I gotta see those I gotta see those live streams. So they still up. Yeah, yeah
I don't delete any of those. So yeah, they're all up and like I said before before May 10th of last year
That's when I got arrested the streams before that cuz I've about 15 and a half months clean. You got a felony
What'd you get a felony for?
drugs
How much were you caught with?
Less than an eight ball of meth
Less than a case. I think it was like 2.9 grams. I think is what it was all together. I'd like three
I'd like I had like three they could have got me for sales because I had like three different little
Containers of it
Well, that sucks
Why I'm grateful that they didn't go after me for that
It's like a crazy, you know, it's a method, it's like a fast-paced thing and it's like
there's a lot of people that are like into like fraud and stuff like that because it's
like it's like it's applied for your addiction and then it's like plus it's like you got
all this energy to figure everything out, yeah, so it's like can be a deadly or a bad
combination in terms of like, you know, getting involved in that stuff.
I'll be right back.
Go ahead and talk to your friend.
You're good.
I think he's looking at my channel.
No, no, no, I'm not. I can't navigate. I'm on my phone.
Oh, I think my, my, I have to go grab my charger real quick. Give me like 10 seconds.
Yeah, no problem.
Okay, I'm back. My computer's about to die.
Anyways, I enjoy this conversation and then and I understand and appreciate what you're coming from when you're saying that
You thought that I was just worried about my internet
aspect of it
Yes, this is the ember that hates LD
And I hate PG I hate both of them
I don't know who that is
I was reading chat
Anyway, so I have done drugs since I was about 21 years old and I obviously I did it off and on.
You know, I have two kids, like there's times where I didn't do drugs. I went to a rehab center
and I've definitely relapsed on several occasions, you know, but I do think being older, I do think the MRT
Class really helped. I do believe drug court really helped because when I first started drug court
I was like, okay, I'm just gonna I'm just gonna do this and then do what I have to do and then you know
Go back to using I told hold on hold on. I know LD. He's the one that he's kind of like the predator here, huh?
Yes, yes, um, anyways, so I
But then I actually started seeing like these success stories coming out of drug court and
people, you know that I used to let you know used to use with you know succeeding and
I'm like and like I said like my life wasn't horrible like I've never been homeless and shit like that
But I was still making drugs a priority in my life and missing out on you know milestones because I'm a four-year-old and and
So there was a lot of these other aspects that you know, I realized especially with MRT
MRT is a good class
I think for people if they really are ready for change with MRT again
I don't know what that is it's moral recognition therapy like it's how do you delve in or delve deep into like
Like how you hurt people and how you want to make amends to people and to being honest to yourself and things like that
Like you really you really deep into
Your own accountability of of what you did while on drugs. That's good
You didn't lose your kids though because some people do well and that's what I'm saying
You know, I'm there's so many aspects of it where I know right now
I'll look it back that I am so fucking lucky and I don't ever want to experience those things
So I do want to be better. I don't want to do drugs. I don't even need drugs like I'm fine without them clearly
I've done it for a year and a half now. Oh, so you're gonna have clean
Yes, 15 and 15 and a half months clean. You got your black key tag, huh?
No, I don't dark I have so far. I'm waiting for the 18 months one now. What's the black one multiple? Yeah, I think it's multiple years
Yeah, I haven't gotten that one yet and unfortunately a lot of my because of my work schedule and things like that
Most of the NA meetings are in the evening and I work in the evenings
So I have to go to like a meetings, but there are two and a meetings that I'm able to go to
One of them I don't go to because the person who runs the chairperson is kind of inappropriate
and makes me feel uncomfortable, but I've already reached out to somebody that can do something
about that.
So there is one meeting that I don't go to.
Thank you, Gotti.
Oh, we got Gotti in the chat.
What's up with Gotti?
He's talking about how we're losing viewers because we're talking about not drama.
The numbers are dropping faster than embers panties for some smack
And thank you, babe, I appreciate it like so I
Understand where random guy is coming around with the mentality of thinking that I'm not done yet
But I don't ever want to have to experience those things and going down the path. I was going it was probably inevitable
And, you know, I don't need to get into a car accident, you know, from speeding to learn to not speed and drive, you know, I don't have to go drink and drive and kill somebody to learn that I don't want to drink and drive.
So there are things I do believe people can learn from other people's mistakes and seeing all this stuff that people have gone through, especially so young like.
I don't ever want to have to experience anything like that. I'm grateful that I haven't and
So I and then I want to be better. I want to be clean. I really do want to be clean
So
Do you still think I'm a bullshitter
No, I just came up the fuck with you. Well, it works. Thank you. You're welcome. You triggered me for a minute
I know I controlled it. I got it under control, but
No, I just gave up
Oh, did you yeah, I gave up why I
Got shit to do
Do you thank you yep?
Yeah, you don't want to be the reason I go relapse right correct. Well. Hey, I don't pop off
Gaudi pop on
You guys have fun. See you. Thank you random guy
Thank you, babe, I think so too
What are you doing psyche?
What are you doing sake? I
Don't think he has his headphones on
How many people are watching now there was 40 I probably ran everybody off because that's how boring I am boring
Where's Arthur? I am boring Arthur. You know why I'm boring because I have so many other things
I might like to worry about I've already been in on here way too long
Like I'm gonna be jumping off here in a minute, but I went for sake to jump on I gotta go get ready for my drug court group
Get cleaned up because I was just cleaning so I'm all fucking dirty
And then I have like three and a half hours of homework
I got to do later after I go to the store
with my old man and my kiddo to get some stuff
that we need for the roof.
So yeah.
Did you get your headphones back on, Psyche?
I'm sorry I was muted.
Yeah, I want to thank you for coming on for the reading.
I want to thank Alex for purchasing the reading.
You know, hopefully.
Thank you for the reading.
I think, you know, she made up with Trisha Licious
and so, you know, and it's like, you know.
We all have ups and downs in relationships
I know that you know, maybe you guys have gone too far past the point of no return
But it would be nice to have a redemption arc or something like that
And I wish you the best of luck with that. Um, no
Just good luck. Um, I hope you know that a lot of us had a pole
On how long we thought you and hers friendship was going to last. I don't know what it ended up being and I honestly
Yeah, you know, but no
I've never heard her say I'm just gonna give someone a break
So I don't know exactly what it is that you need to do for her to fill the for the redemption to occur
But I know not sitting there talking shit about her constantly with everybody else obviously will make it
I hope I like never did that because I think she did nothing wrong to me and it's like absolutely
It's like she wants and she never said oh, just like stay away from me. It was just like
We have a difference of opinion about like certain people and it's like, you know, like with beta like I don't
hate beta and it's like I don't want to like hurt beta and stuff like that but at the same time I don't
Think that like we're gonna ever be that said like these are ever gonna be the same again
And it's like I think I just wanted to leave I wanted to leave things with beta on a positive or like a more positive
More than they were
Just so it's like I didn't know it's all this negative energy there, but
Now it's turned into like maybe I'm seen as I'm in love with beta or something like that and I'm not I'm very good
Well, you know all I can say is
You're very new when it comes to to Alex and
She
This is what she does, you know, I'm not I'm not I am honestly
I'm not gonna sit up here and talk about bad about her with you because I know that's not
That's not the time or the place for that
so
She is going to want you to probably stay away from Vita. And if that's not something you want to do be who you are
She'll eventually learn to respect that more than you just giving in to be a friend with her
You know what I mean because you're gonna have there's gonna be more hiccups like this in the future
Just just know that and so I don't want to be the
Everything it's hard for me to like hate people and it's like also like
so many relationships of mine, people have gotten in the middle of it and then it's like
people pick a choice and it's like usually the choice is not me you know and then that person
hates me and that's like so I just hate that being done to me and so I really like want to like
try to avoid like doing it to the people even if I just try to stay away like keep a distance from
some people like you know I still don't want to like hate them and like have animosity so I don't
know it's just and also like um
Thing that is I don't know. I don't know like she's a cut she gets focused on some people for something like some things
And it's like you can't like some people you can't fix a
You don't really agree with something like that because they're so certain they're right about stuff
Give it an intuition or whatever and maybe they are maybe they are and then we maybe we see different things
Okay, okay, she gets focused on people. Yes, but I'll have you know that
This is probably that I've seen in the last like four years the fourth or fifth
time that she has gone back and forth was like Eutrisha, Controla, and just Jen.
So...
I and she deletes a lot of her well not a lot of them
But when she gets good with somebody sometimes she'll go back and delete some of the videos that she made to the person
Or if she doesn't like them, so she has a lot of back and forth with people
This is really like the fifth time that she's
I think she has like this really great quality,
which is like this journalist kind of energy,
but then at the same time, the journalist is also
like the snoopy investigator and like, you know,
goes to expose them too much and stuff like that.
I mean, about people, right?
I mean, I can, like journalists,
kind of a journalist personality,
but she like does have,
she's a very polished broadcaster.
No, she is.
I've said that many times, even I've said that many times,
she's very articulated.
and well-educated and has a very uh domineering presence when she is on screen or talking about
something like I it's very impressive and I say all the time like she could do so much good with
that right because I think that there are like all these like you know these things especially
the student these things that she's encouraged about in the happening in the world she is kind of
Whole like it's basically there's gonna be people that are involved, right? But it also it's like the bigger issue of the
Being itself like bring intended like that. That's what it is to me like it's like it's not really about the people that are like doing these things it's about like
They're done they have they have backing that they
The highest you know highest realm they have to come back and I don't so it's interesting. It's like
Yeah, I like our crusade it's just like
I know, I thought he was to offer her a reason.
What does, what does articulated doesn't mean thing that is?
Like, I can't say she's very well articulate, can I?
That doesn't make any sense to me.
I'm gonna look it up now, before I look dumb arguing over it.
I know.
Yeah.
I love Google.
I think Google is like well spoken, yeah.
Having two or more sections connected by a flexible joints, but it also says two of an idea or feeling expressed or put into words
One of the first articulated emotions that you will hear from a child
So I'd say it was 50% that I used it wrong, but there's still 50% I used it correctly
My intention of the word the way that I used it was correct however
I should have said she, yeah, I got what they're saying.
Whatever.
Suck it.
Yeah, it's good.
I mean, it's good.
It's all good.
It was grammar police, right?
Grammar police.
It's okay, you know, but yeah.
Thank you, Kate.
A young age never checked my mother's grammar
or I was just getting out of smack.
So, I don't really correct people's grammar ever.
But,
Yeah, I'm sure mine's always perfect either.
I don't think Jem.
Jem is outrageous, true.
Well, I'd rather that someone tell me that I'm using it wrong now
and argue and find out that I'm wrong and keep using it wrong
and then everyone fucking laugh at me as though
I do appreciate when I get corrected.
I don't even know if I'm a leviathan.
But, you know, I was her mod and it's like, you know, I just like knew like I should not correct her about certain things
But she used to call it
Ontario she'd be like, oh, well, this is the 22 major Arcadia and we have the you know, the you know the minor Arcadia and it's like
You know, it's not the right word, but it's like is it really?
It's Arcana, you know, but she would call Arcadia, but I never corrected her
Yeah, yeah, but some people can't handle being corrected. So, um, I do have to jump off here. I've been on here way too long
Yeah, definitely. Yeah, I'm on back and I don't know if I remodeled you yet, but just comment in the chat
Oh, yeah, I'll do it right now. I'll be right back. All right. I push. Oh, uh,
Yeah, this is my other account. So I'll come back on my other of my other ones
Okay, I'll let you know because it's my second count. This is the one I use when people ban me. So
All right, bye you guys thank you everybody
So, let's see. I think I wanted to show you something I made last night. I made a few last night
In the city of mirrors and smoke
Psyche walks where the ghost lights choke Every face, a mask, every word, a spell
Every promise spun in the web of Jezebel Bandits whisper blessings, thieves wear crowns
The prophets lost their maps to these haunted towns
He's been bound by silk, by sin, by code But his spirit still burns down every
In the web of Jezebel, he almost disappears, but the panther comes, all teeth and tears, shadow mercy, eyes like night eye, cuts the cords, brings him back to life, he survived the cryptids, the narcissist charm.
The story bends
He's dance with severs shared wine with ghosts
He almost fades, but the panther roars and the spell decays through the maze of mirrors through smoke and fire
He walks out laughing untouched by the pyre
He's seen the fangs, the gilded deceit, but truth is around
The story bends
Every color is a key
Every tear or code
Every death or rebirth
On the winding road
And the panther whispers in a voice so low
They can't kill
J'ai bouchés un paire
Gusha's mouth boy. I kind of look like Force Sanderson's sister a little bit, I don't know.
Yes, my love?
Mexico, of course I'll give you a mug shot.
Mugos shut up.
It was love, not me.
I'm shadow band again.
Pop, pop, pop, pop.
Bro mute your mic, then boom.
Drop a bass line dirtier than the chat.
Up, up, up.
Ghost is crashing out.
Smashing raptors like me.
People from an undisclosed stage
Natalie being backfussed behind head
Mods praying Lord, not again
Welcome to the Paniverse baby hold your ground
Where the chaos hums like a feedback sound
We don't know who's sane, who's banned or blessed
But the vibes unholy and always possess
Scotty causing from the bone
Brags he just dropped a cosmic load
Live in HD
Authors they're just smiling sweet
Y'all need Jesus or at least some sleep
and it's all so true ghost is connected canada dried time down rando's still
typing wait to be that just ban me laughter static cat me out in stream
noise it was too tight per second you like the way better idea I like it too
I sell you Lloyd Ryan
You chase my ghost through neon crowns
And yeah you know I rig the spray with trickster hands
A terror deck of sleight of sand
You bet your soul on a phantom vow
I warned you though
So I hex my stars for a fair game
I'm the fool
Your love's an ocean of curse to trust
It drags me under sweet undertow
Still I go, still I go
The rogue inside me runs with storms
Tearing down the tiles we swore were born
It's like truth, la la la la la you, the charm that breaks through, la la la la la you,
my doom, my muse, my view.
Hold spell, new lease, you breathe and I can't breathe.
Lock the door, flood the gate, click too late, but still
I fall like
sections that switch side
Wow, look at that with twins you are one fix your hair man cousin head
it's going on, it's going on chat.
Thank you real quick. Yeah, I don't know why you were saying I said that you suck. I I stopped lip-flopping
I mean you went rogue as a mob before and then like before though, okay, well, I forgive you you're you're my cute little Filipino friend
Thank you, and you're my cute little pack sucker. Thank you. Oh, yeah
Actually, no, no, you're not you're not I can't believe what you said it. Well, I know
You're making me blush right now, dude.
Okay.
Well, would you have to say to Gotti?
No, nothing at all.
I was wearing the wig.
Would you have sex with me?
Real quick.
Sandman did the day was on your panel here and he was saying,
I'm not afraid of you.
You think I'm afraid of you?
I don't bow down to you.
You're a piece of shit.
Well, what are you talking about?
You said it to me?
Yeah.
You didn't hear him?
What he's like, what he says is not that relevant to me because he's a fool, you know, he plays Roblox
What he plays Roblox
You're lying. Yeah, he plays the game at Roblox. Oh, that's probably plays with his nephews. Oh my god
that's weird adults are allowed to play like it's like saying you know parents
can't go to the Disney where they're just gonna let the kids go to the movie
themselves no they have to like let them know take them to the movie and so
No, I make fun of his hobby. That's his hobby. Why are you making fun of him? Well, I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding
Roblox is like, you know, it's somebody named Brandon who's he was like who's actively on the monkey app
And then he's he's been at Sam ever going on the roadblocks. What the fuck is roadblocks anyway? It's like minecraft, right?
It's like a minecraft game
It's for kids. I have no idea what it means. It's like too complicated
Everything's like so
the
It's like still the computer. It's like not I mean, it's like, you know, even like that, uh,
That, uh, the dateline catch a predator stuff and they had this divine or that's not what is it called them perverted justice or whatever
We did that that that you know that lesbian woman that looked like a 13 year old boy and stuff and say hey, what's up?
Can you want some cookies and brownies and stuff and then it's like
Hello, I'm Chris Hansen comes have a see sir
Mother brains
Yeah, so, um, you know, it's like
Yeah, you could sue them for entrapment. That's right. Well, the guy that committed suicide
I think or I'm not himself his family did like probably sue because he was like he just ran home and you know
I'm alive himself after he like you know met Chris handsome. Well, he deserved it. I mean like
There's some people that were like seriously, um, like mentally ill on that show like, you know, like
Like really like ill like there's one guy they caught like twice in like two days or whatever, but he was like
Genuinely like not they still fucking do it
And that's why I don't get the whole intro
That's why nowadays when I was on the internet. It was like there's like the Wild West
It was like because the parents didn't my parents had no idea of anything on the internet
I was like I was just like, you know, like it was restoring while nowadays all the parents were like pretty much grew up on the internet
So they know everything like they know how to like, you know, look at every search history. They know how to
You know parental controls, right? It's like, I mean they're responsible. You know, it's catching these you know
It's catching these guys now youtubers they're going after these guys and they're beating the fuck out of them
That's not that's not good either because that's like, you know
They go ahead and like prosecute them like you know have the police in whatever no no no no they need a fucking beating first
I don't think that that just takes away from the justice system kind of there was one guy in a wheelchair
Did you see the guy in the wheelchair? He was like
Chris K like special fucked up. He's like a quadriplegic. He was trying to be like a 13 year old boy
So it's been a joke, but you know use of his body
What is this person you know, they can't take that person in the prison because it's like they don't have a ramp in jail and stuff
I mean, it's like so they
It would never even do anything.
He's already in prison, basically, but not like that, man.
Fuck these people.
I got no sympathy for these people.
Do you want to, like, stay out of prison?
Did you become a logical egic?
And like, you can, like, or just, like, you know,
they will never get arrested for anything because of this.
You don't fuck with kids, man.
It's fucked up.
Well, yeah, of course, but it's like,
we want the justice system taking care of it,
so it's like, some people can't see it.
Like, there's no justice, man.
Where you been lately?
There's no fucking justice in the world.
You got to make it wrong.
You're gonna take Madison to your own hands well sometimes but that's just as a not serve
because that's a bit you know vigilante justice that sometimes you know in cases where it's
like you know but then it's like people then the crowd becomes the judge jury executioner
the crowd is a really stupid thing now you got to get your own personal justice look
at this guy this guy broke into a house.
He uh went into the kids room. He stabbed this fucking six-year-old and ran in the head right in the head
You heard that one and then they let him go. They let the guy go
I mean it's like I mean now you can kidnap people and stuff like that like in some some states
They'll just let you off like you know on a 24-hour hold after something like that
And they should call it going stuff
It actually kidnap each other with all kinds of stuff like you know like um you couldn't like get away with all these kind of crimes
Lenora's kissing her
I don't case the wig
Into the wig. She thinks I'm a new person. Hi. She's fucking. She's role-playing. Yeah
Like the blonde wig
I'm gonna get the nor little blonde wig too. I'll be great. Yeah, put a little hair on it. Let's see how it looks
Yeah, put a little your hair on her
We said oh, she's running away
Okay, you're so pretty
She likes it
She's hurrying. She's a new bitch. She's hurry. I'm a new bitch. There you go. Psych is a new bitch, everyone
I in honor of me being a new new woman. Can I have sex with you?
No, you don't have enough money pal. We look cute
You need more money than you have
I mean, I would need to be you know, you need to be like Elon Musk rich
You need to at least have like what is it 12 zeros after the one?
Well, you're a big zero
I'm a big zero. No God is a big zero because it's actually that God is like every like everything
But I think nothing I think it's like imagine a circle and everything is contained in the circle
You just call me a big zero and now you're trying to fix it
So what's up with them Dodgers? Oh, okay. Yeah deflect
Never since the wigs psyche you've turned into a fucking like a diva, dude
People can't even talk to you anymore. It's like you're in fucking diva mode. I feel like the goddess of love
Yeah, see it's gone to your fucking head
But then that that Denmark I said he wanted to have sex with me and then he just said
It's not like he just wanted to beat me up and leave me like die on the side of the road
That's what it all it's always like that. I thought we're romantic with date those
I mean, I need to be like driven to the hospital
They beat the fuck out of them they laugh at you, right? Well, that's like very nice. No
There's actually there's a movie got you got you got to see it and you I think you would love this movie
It's um the British movie. I think it's called the sui Cide theory. Okay, just watch that movie
But uh, it's suicide theory. Yeah, and there's a bit. I'll just tell you that but there's a there's a gay guy in it and like
Part of the movie like he like meets this bartender
And it gave bar or whatever the bartender hitting on him and then he goes to like meet these guys for sex and just something very bad happens
I just I'll say but it's like that is like probably like that's the Matthew Shepard thing
There's like a lot of and it's like I think some of these guys that do that are questioned their own sexuality
I'm morphine to the Lilith character. Oh Paul knows Paul knows
Yeah
My alley, this type of movie, sounds great.
My, oh yeah, you would like it.
I can't wait to watch it.
Okay, watch it. I swear you'll like it. I love it.
I don't think so. It's not my cup of tea.
I like blood. I like a lot of blood.
Did I ever tell you how much I like blood?
Is there blood in this movie?
Yes, it's about this guy, he's trying to like...
I'm on a live himself, but every time he survives and so he hires this like hitman to like try to do it and the hitman
You know that's it's having trouble right and so it's like there's a theory about you know
SCYC ideas that we have to get so that's part of it
But there is it's really interesting move. They'll make you really think I'm making really comedy
No, well, it's kind of like a dark comedy in a way
I get everything there are funny parts to it and it's like but it's like basically kind of like just like trippy and like that
I'm like uh
really like a spiritual, got a really interesting spiritual aspect to it.
I think you would really dig it.
Fast flashing out in my personality is an order that wasn't able to manifest until now.
I know, but you know what, a wig is an amazing thing for bringing out a personality disorder.
I mean, it's like now I'm able to...
Well, that's the thing. I was like, I was told that, oh, well, I think Vita is your Lilith.
And as I said, well, that would be very dangerous, that would make her very dangerous because
like when the onma, which is the male's inner female, which is oftentimes repressed and
projected out onto women of like maybe a...
Maybe passive characters so that it's like they don't they can take on any kind of mirror you throw at them, right?
And so it's like
It's like the fairy. It's like what is a fairy? I don't know. It's it's a much like an alien a spirit
So it's like, you know, it's all the kind of the same thing, you know, I came up
I came up with a pretty good theory about why you and beat up beefing right now
Tell me and I wanted to run it by you see what you thought about it
As you know, you know, I used to be a clinical psychologist. Okay. Yeah, so
So it's gonna be a little personal. Don't don't get like angry about it
I'm not saying it to be malicious. What is gonna be like a Freudian theory or you more Jungian
No, this is gonna be a professional theory
No, I'm saying Freudian psychology is about like, you know, I'm not using Freud. I'm not using Freud with this
This is a personal professional opinion. Okay
So tell me if I'm wrong about any of this
So recently within the year, I think at least I think last year you said you meant you lost your father, right?
Yeah, okay, and she had she had also lost her mother last year, I believe
No, no, she lost her mother when she was a young girl like 15 years old. Oh, I'm sorry. I thought it was more
Alexandra lost her father this year
No, no, no, I thought she had lost her mother recent, but I think it's still it's still bothersome. I believe
You both you both basically bonded over that the loss of the parent
So when you guys bonded over that you became really close. I think you did at least
After that after that bonding you guys found out that basically
you don't like each other too much.
No, I think, well, right,
but now looking back on things,
she was like,
Just like when she said the other night she's like oh that poem I wrote a poem about or something
It was about you I posted on my community wall and it was like this really like lovey-dovey thing
And I was like well that's interesting because it's like sounds like a love poem and then it's like then the next day
She's like well. Why do you think I'm in love with you? I was like well
He told me like that poem was about me
She's like I never said that and I have it on tape
I have it on my you know honor when I said what she said on her show and so then she's so then she's like
So that's kind of a manipulation. That's a big thing if she was lying about what she's not she's been caught in the life
saying that it was for me or something like that and then it turned out it was that what can that
be besides manipulation thing and she was crying when she said it you know and stuff like that so
it was like I just felt real bad but I'm really sensitive to like you know you know and I think
there's something in the brain that just like when a female cries there's something that's like
like what's going to stop. I think Jamie has already the trauma bonding that's what you did. Yeah it
could be that too. You bonded with her after your trauma of losing your father and then it turns sour.
No, this is where this is where we are everybody has to deal with it now
Bunch of people like during my women at my fault like I didn't a better after my father passed away
But there's people that I met during that time that it's like I'm not friends
I'll talk to her right into her face, but she doesn't want, she doesn't want to talk except on her terms, like, oh, yeah, like, you know, at certain times on her show, and then like, I'm on the show just to talk about certain things, and she won't want to talk about anything.
And so, and then she talks about me all the time. And then even Arthur was like, she was like talking about me, but not talking about, they're not saying my name, but they're just referring to me, referring to me, referring to me, and making these like insight jokes and stuff.
Stop talking about psyche and so it's even like other people are perceiving that it's like something talking about me, right?
That's kind of
Don't get me wrong. I'm not talking about beat. I'm talking about the problem that you guys have there's a difference
I'm talking I'm trying to get to the root of the fucking cause of why you guys have happened for so much beef
And why you can't break away from each other
well
Well, it's like the devil in the fool, which I just played it's like, you know, it's like I said
I was the devil and she was the fool and it's her
Yeah, but you you can say you can say things like that, but you can't put a definition on what the problem is
She's the devil you're the fool
I don't think any of you, I don't think any of you's have traveled through the nine circles of hell, according to Dante.
We're about to be taken there with you talking.
Go ahead, Vanguard, go ahead.
We're in the seventh level.
Don't say hire anything, don't fucking greet anyone.
It's going to be a bullshit.
Go on to your fucking boss, go ahead.
I wish I was a head in the jar.
I'd live forever.
What's his name?
What's his name with white hair?
And why are you all got a fucking white wig on there?
My name is Freya.
That was a blow.
I'm pulled by a chariot of black cats.
White, white-haired people.
I have a really expensive golden cat.
Made by some dwarves.
Why the fuck are you snorting all the time, man?
What are you snorting?
I'm really attracted to these dwarves that make gold.
Dwarfs in order to get my apologies. I'll can we just reset sites?
Why are you in the white wig and why is goatee's new avatar him with white hair?
I'm paying homage to him
You're wearing a wig too, you're wearing a fucking wig too. What are you talking about bank card?
What? That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig. That's not a wig
The possum yes a possum not a panda. No, the thing that scared it was a panda
But anyway
Pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop, pop
From the bone Braggs he just dropped a cosmic load
Burning bridges living HD authors. They're just smiling sweet
Y'all need Jesus or at least some sleep
You're actually going to hell for 800 bucks
The courting courting and that is very simple. Come on. Anyway goatee house life doing with the richie feet
So they do good life is grants or life is grant
We got peace in the Middle East after all these years of the three thousand
Yeah, yeah, I was gonna blow her up and make Trump look like a cunt cuz he didn't get
I'll send you to
Anyway, it's nice to see you go team with all jokes aside
Are you doing okay? Are you? Yeah? Yeah, I can't complain. I got you know, I could walk
Mrs. Doubtfire
Well, first of all, I don't sound like Mrs. Don't fire you fucking dumb fucking
You can't you can't unless he's like, you know gained 1,000 pounds within the last two years or
Cracked himself out. He looks he looks like a normal human being
Yes, you look normal vanguard or no?
Yes, I'm very normal, but I am a Viking. I am a Scots person. I hate Donald Trump in Benjamin yet. No, I'm very
Nobody's perfect, man
Yeah, but it's good to see it. It's good to see it psych
Do you know what what do you think about three I Atlas you think we're gonna be invaded
What's it doing? What's it doing right now on the other side of the sun recharging for like a final blast?
Yeah, my name's coming back. My name's coming back
Explain to me. I'm kind of stupid explain to me how this thing can come flying into the solar system, right?
and then slingshot around the sun and go flying out.
I think NASA is a bunch of bullshit just making shit up.
But how do comets keep coming back every like what?
Haley's coming back every 80 years.
Well, first of all, Three Isles is not a comet.
It's an interstellar visitor.
A bit like a comet, but it's not a comet.
Is that a visitor unless it's got some conch?
But you're going by what NASA is telling you.
I mean I I I actually look at what European Space Agency see another fucking agency see
what if what if the sun throws off its orbit a little bit and comes flying into Mars or
Already could do anything as far as we know. Yeah, we don't know what it's doing on the other side right now
Anyway, I've known goatee for a quite a few years and goatee is quite a nice person when he's not been a cunt
Isn't that right goatee? Yeah, which is what 50% of the time?
Really I'm a cunt 80% of the time
yeah well that's rude dude that's fucking rude you're not I'm just being a
bitch you are you're fucking it's the hair he called me a zero and now he's
calling me a cunt it's worse now it's like I was mean as a guy from hero to
zero like that go to you I mean come on go to every single day I'm very
I hate it when people make fun of me.
Oh, God, I'll make one of you all at a time, but we're cool.
I don't know what to do, I think you should do it.
I'll do one of you is get out of the wheelchair, right?
One day.
You got to remind me of that kid in Mac and me,
and I'm like that, hey, oh, thank you.
I'd never saw the movie, but I know what everybody's talking about with that shit. I saw the clip. That's fucked up
And he goes over the cliff. Yeah. Yeah, what do they do? They just want to torture the fuck out of that kid
You know, they know they don't know that can the wheelchair or the alien again the wheelchair
Well, that kid was fine
I mean basically the movie was trying to like it was McDonald's got a chance to make a movie and they like this had to rip off
E.T. and so
And so basically has the same plot of E.T. except like, you know
Way less of a budget Stephen Hawkins Stephen Hawkins get AI'd and takes the fuck out of McDonald's and goes up in the sky
What the fuck?
Well, hey, you guys believe a William Shadiner went into space. Yeah, that was cool
Nothing that fucking blue origin does doesn't go into space. It's not even the calming line to be honest come on
It was cool that he did it, whatever he did.
But it wasn't, it was like all of a sudden they're like,
oh here he comes and then they see like,
they cut away and then all of a sudden
they're just drinking champagne and they don't show.
And they're like, you just sit in like this room
where you see someone else.
Let's not get onto Katie Perry out fucking staging,
fucking that cunt that owns Amazon.
What's he saying?
That was fake.
That was all fake.
That was staged.
I don't believe any of that.
No.
The whole thing was fake.
Wow
You think that bitch was gonna jeopardize her fortune by marrying this dude no chance
Did you see the funny fact though, when Jeff Bezos went to open up the capsule, it was
opened already and then they shut it again.
Yeah, yeah, I saw that.
That's fake.
They just went into it.
I don't think so.
Yeah, it was fake.
The only place it takes you is to Chinese factory.
Sorry.
I don't think we'll live to see anybody on Mars.
Well
It's a one-way trip
Six months
It's gonna have to be like those send like a thousand optimists is up there the robots
Well, as long as there's loads of potatoes just like the Martian said
Martian where he survived on potatoes for fucking what
Don't mutated
Well, I don't think he's ever seen the Martian with the what what's his name again?
Matt Damon
You want to see a Martian, I'll show you a Martian. This is a Martian right here. Oh, keep your cock in your pants, please please please please
Hey show psyche that potato that you found
Scythe would automatically kick me when he found out what a fucking problem
Thank them for being I mean I
Don't want to talk about potatoes for an hour, right? I
Don't want to talk about
It's cock or things like that. I
Don't want God to get God he has this picture of this cross-eyed woman on it. I don't know who that is full woman
picture
So no, but guys
Out of New York, came a storm on wheels, rolling in smooth with the mafia feels, Cuban cigar lit like it's temper, pizza in one hand, hot dog for dinner said psyche, I'm bored, had to switch the scene, left some poor woman screaming on live stream, trolled her down to the void and back, then crashed my show like a heart attack, gotty, made man, troking, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling, trolling
But they're still my friends
Yeah love, you got it
Till the bitter end we fight
We troll, but we friends
Forever my friend
He's God with the lowercase g in a wheelchair still stomping through the live feed
Bout of your king while smoking that leaf
Laughing at chaos like it's comic relief brought spunky too now that trolls a gem mean one sweet ones
They all jumped in cameras glitching chat on fire mods begging me to cut the wire, but nah, I like my circus
I love this mess every trolls just a test stop and that's got you
Absurd and free, but deep down you got loyalty
Gotti, made man, troll, king, mafia, soul
Rollin' through panels like he's in control
Discord, army, Amish, Italian, Mormon, blend
They dangerous, wild, but they still my friends
Yeah, love you, Gotti, till the bitter end
We fight, we troll, but we friends
Forever my friend
You called me a fraud
Then defended my clown Spam my chat
Then held it down You got layers
Like a deep dish slice Under all that shade
a heart made of ice and maybe rice so let's light that cigar raise the mic another night of chaos
welcome to psych you brought the drama the heat the fun and weirdly it feels like you're the one
nope not the one hey psych you want to know psych psych you're mic man we cannot hear a damn word
Sorry, I didn't mean to yell.
that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the one that's the
I wouldn't talk to a person-to-person rather than listen to rumors and stuff, so.
You could talk there in November.
I know there are things that is nice to see you, sir.
Things are very rational.
Hello, guys.
Thing that is, can you just say, can you use it once and for all?
Right there, that sounds great.
Once and for all, the thing that is, are you using mind control on Joe Shipley?
Well, I don't have to, right?
I mean, what are you doing like? Why are you what? Why are you harassing Alex? Oh, like who?
Alexandra, I'm harassing her. Please. Have you said things about her on on on your show?
And then every day every time like people are doing something bad like you're around
What is that about? What?
What does that mean like when someone else is talking bad about her and chat I happen to be in chat
Is that what you're saying? Yeah
common denominator
I just want to make sure
But my opinion has been based purely on on her actions
Sound a bit cool to she can't comment on what other people are saying is that cool tissue like
Come on. Sorry, no comment. Oh, yeah. No, just just on her actions and just from what I've seen not based on any
Oh
You talk negatively I'm saying about her so maybe I haven't been positive if that's what you mean like I haven't been praising her
Okay, why talk about it all?
with it
When someone tells me that hey, she's saying this shit about you whatever I just say. Yeah, you know, she's nuts
What do you want?
Specifically the stuff about you like recently or yeah, yeah, have you heard of it?
Myself. No, I don't listen. Yeah. Yeah, it's better off not to comment. Yeah, it's like because
I but I just don't know but it's like what I saw it was that you had kind of a blank expression now when you heard Joe Shipley
Say those words. Well, I don't know what you're talking about. Honestly, okay
So you were okay
So you were on beta's panel and you you were saying oh that was fun
We just did some fart trivia, right and then Joe Shipley's like, you know what Alex?
If you mess with beta, I'm gonna unalive it. Okay. I'm gonna say that he said that right
And you were sitting right there, and you just had a blanket brush on me. It's I'll be you know beat this channel before
Recall that
But it sounds like there's a bit of a camp here you're on your in this camp or you're in that camp
Yeah, there's some that going on regardless of what anyone said Alex is showing herself to be a great friend
Do you say I know she is many times?
I'm trying to figure out like is there is something else besides like this
So I'm gonna pull the clip but it's based on what you've been doing lately. That's all
but what have I been doing like all I did was like you've been trying you've been trying to go back to
you've been trying to get back with beat it and I think it is on my show he's a member of my channel
and I've never had a problem with him other than like you know that spunky thing and so I don't
quite understand well I'm never a member of anybody's channel I just go everywhere because
I wouldn't pay to be part of anything brother that way because I am the vanguard
The mic has disappeared again. You cried on her shoulder about beta and then you want to get back with beta
Making her look like a fool. You basically that's what it's what's been going on
I wasn't trying to get back with me. I was trying to put things on a piece of level and I think it didn't go anywhere
Okay, I'm gonna show you this clip. Okay. Hold on a second. Oh, no, don't do that to me dude. I gotta go. I'm working
Hey, well, I'm gonna show a clip of something now hold on is it a long clip. No, it's a short clip
It just even is on the on the on the show hold on
Long clip. He always says it's not a lot 10 minute clip
Or in my
Is this something that a lot of you need to even know about no because you wouldn't believe it
But here's what you do need to believe in what you do need to know
There are people on this planet who have something called the ability of compulsion.
They can compel others to do and say things that they normally wouldn't.
And that is what happened tonight.
Let me go ahead and play the clip and then we're going to talk about this a little bit
more.
it's just saying that I was far trivia that we're getting into in the chat all of a sudden
it's very interesting I must say
you guys look familiar
I
Oh, oh, look at his face there. He smiles when she says hook you up bitch
I'm constantly reading chat and reacting to chat man. They're like smiling at the joke
I can't leave for a minute to go like what the fuck
No, it's not, I'm actually like my own like my issue and it's like this is like really
Stupid and I gotta get her out of my head is like I trust it like like I try to help and trust somebody and like
I think Mimi really hurt me. I think that's what it is
because I can't understand that full saturation but anyway that's that but no I'm gonna move on from
it and I want to play and just like you know but I don't know it's like kind of it kind of drained
me because it was like so I was like so out of like it was like left field
Yeah, I bet you are drained
I'm sure you're very trained and it's gonna get worse
There are very decent but yeah, yeah, I wanted to touch on that psyche. So yeah, this thing things that is he seems like a really like
You know calm boomer he cams up and everything but the more I see of him. He's he's kind of sneaky a little obsessive
Nice
You're delicious you're you know you've got these double standards you try to be this moral compass and yet
You know you're okay and all this bullshit when it's the people on your side quote-on-quote
Yes, thank you
lack of better words, yeah
I'm the only non-american here
Shut up, you fuck up, Bangor
You blow with the wind is what he's saying
I'm the only non-american here
No, you shut this guy up
Shut the fuck up
You shut your fucking mouth
You're an asshole
You're a dark American fucker
I'm trying to cook here and you're just being this fucking
Scottish whatever you are
Meets you have so much folks. Oh, I am so I can't work with this guy
If he means if he means the two sides between
Beta and psych I'm on on either side
Right, but it means the two sides between beta and Alexander. I'm on beta side. Okay
Okay, like is that we all disagree about like certain like, you know, tax tax or the person that people are doing on like
Well, you don't be the psych as you go to her channel all the time. That's why okay your friends would be like that's why yeah
Not make sense. I don't know you're biased. You're biased. You're not like
Like I said, I'm all good. I'm on beat aside, but the next part of it is
Does random white guy or anybody else comment on absolutely every single thing?
And why should I comment on everything right? But it's a specific things that are like on stream
So it's like it's actually like okay, man. That's certainly didn't look good. I don't know if there's any trickery going on there
But I don't recall it a hundred percent sure that she would not I certainly don't recall it. I'll say that
Yeah, I don't go for that kind of
Concentration playing with Joe's mind trying to get him to say I'm looking on the side here on this monitor. I've got like
Another monitor over here, and I've got a browser open. I've got other things open. I'm constantly like looking at stuff
I may have been looking at code. Sometimes I'm looking at the same time
I mean it kills somebody I would have heard that like that's one say that what did I say when I came back though
When I when I address the stream again, I said something, but it wasn't loud enough. You can't hear that. What did I say?
You say I just I just saw you smiling. Did I say something to Joe? It certainly seemed like I did
Right anyway, are we analyzing a smile?
Yeah, I think that means
Can you can you agree with me when there's you see some discourse?
And certain coats get a butt hurt and throw the toys out the pram
And I don't believe what you said. There's no discourse there. I mean, is looking talking about man
I don't know
Are you trying to say something like just without saying it like just you just spit it out, please
People that feel that way around here, I understood that there were words that you said vanguard
But in the order that you put them in I didn't understand what that meant
Well, yeah, so you're a part of the committee that says if you don't believe what I say go fuck yourself
Keep talking into the wind and what the fuck do I care?
Joe just says things for a fact
Know Joe has said to me before several times. I'm gonna on the live you
I was Joe's pretty rowdy that night from what I remember, but he's rowdy a lot in regardless
You can't say it. You can't say it on a panel without taking the heat. I agree
Well, I mean it's like I mean and it's I don't think I kicked him off for saying that stuff
But he said it about somebody who takes a damn serious. Yeah, I know he shouldn't
Definitely, but I'd say now the thing that is is like being kind of pulled into it like that kind of is like
Not he's smiling again
So do you have this is ridiculous because I don't have any way that's violent or anything like that. I've never
Green
So I mean this is it's pretty ridiculous man. I disavow what he said does that make you feel better? I don't know what to say
Right, right, right. Never mind your personal, never mind your personal gripes. Never mind your personal gripes.
Never mind your personal gripes. What do you have a sense of humor at all?
Ria, do you have me? Come on.
Hang on, we're analyzing his face. Watch.
Go ahead and play the clip, and then we're going to talk about this a little bit more.
And that's all this fart trivia that we're getting in in chat all of a sudden. It's very interesting. I must say
Fuck out of Janzer Myers. She wants to fuck with beta, then she's fucking with me
I am playing anymore
But you want to talk with me? What did that say? What did I say?
He said I'm he said he I'm not playing anymore and you said what did I say when I turned back
Why does not that not have any volume, but Joe is
Anything that's clipped in
I bet you anything Alexander I do not trust her
I don't trust her trivia. I don't trust her. This is fake. I'll say it right now. This is fake. It's
I am playing anymore. No
But you want to fuck with me and I'll kill you
Shut up Joe. Can you shut the fuck up? I can't leave for a minute to go like brush my teeth. What the fuck?
No, it's not I
Actually like my own like my issue and it's like this is like really stupid
And I gotta get out of my head is like I trust it like like I try to help and trust somebody and like I think me
Me really hurt me. I think that's what it is
because I can't understand that whole situation but anyways that's it but no I'm gonna move on from
it and I want to play and just like you know but I don't know it's like kind of it kind of drained
me because it was like so I was like so out of like it was like left field yeah I don't think you
noticed her yeah I bet you are drained Miss Mustapavi I'm sure you're going to get worse
It's gonna get a lot worse another fail by Alexander. What can I say?
For tonight, you never join that panel again and do not join any more panels that feature
This all this are killer this man
I want telling people name of this particular man
Landon LaPlante learn that the hard way, but I want you to
Joe is talking
Whenever this and you're cool with it. I haven't heard you disavow anything
You disavow her this fucking moment
I don't believe that she's trying to dox it. Yes, she is. She just said she wants my real name
Yeah, not to give out to anybody like fuck off man. Don't give me that shit
You disavow her this moment. I don't believe in doxing. I don't disavow her this moment
I'll say I don't believe in doxin. I hope that she would never dox you or anything like that, but I don't think that
When you talk about
All of it punishes
Some of the most
I've never spoken
privately with this man to my knowledge I've never had anything to do with this
man thing that is but he's been making some moves lately who is he and why is
he here and why is he smiling while a death threat is being issued toward me
on public figure, Bita Mostafavi's panel.
Now, as soon as this happened,
the person who clipped this
told me that he bounced.
I guess he thought no one was gonna clip this,
no one was gonna notice.
Do you know that there is something real called a warlock?
I was thinking the same thing that's what this one is. I was just thinking that master for flowers of Manchester
He absolutely is I have seen some of the worst things said not only in regards to me
But in regards to others he touched his nose present
He always smiles, nods, and you can almost see his mind working.
Also, he looks substantially younger than his age, energy vampire.
But a little bit more than that, he's a solid warlock.
I'm not against warlocks, I'm not against witches, everyone has a gift, but it's how
you use it or how you abuse it.
Yes, agreed.
Negative.
This is very negative.
You cannot have this person on your panel anymore, Mostafavi.
I mean, you can, I can't force you not to,
but guess what bitch, lawsuit time.
You wanna sue everybody else?
Well, solid death threat, and there's been others.
I mean, I personally don't have any DMs
when it comes to you and clumsy,
but as I told clumsy,
he doesn't need to worry about getting that cell phone fixed.
Anyway, Jimmy Rizzo says the proof as to why, before, but now I do.
Right there, fuck.
Vanguard, you are an embarrassment to the British people.
Riza, go fuck yourself, 2.0.
Are you talking to my mods in a negative way?
Is Riza my mod? Let me check.
Well, could you tell your mods talk to other mods in a are you a warlock thing?
Is he a warlock?
The whole thing that is he left. He disappeared using the lower chat. Are you a warlock thing thing?
What is going on with those empty ultra hand signals you're using?
Making Joe say things because Joe is kind of like
I'm known Alexander me is for years. I really have
beautiful smart woman yes a very loyal friend yes from what I could see
What and now I see her point about a thing that is he's now no I do and I look at him
He has a little guilty expression on his face like
Does any kind of he kind of like looks a little bit like hmm. He has his hands, but maybe it looks like something more than
I'm not sure he reminds me of the uncle from bewitched remember that guy
Paul the Paul in Paul and yeah, you reminds me of that guy. Yeah, hey, Samantha
Uncle Arthur and he's like a warlock, but it's like
Uncle Arthur is and like Carl are powerful warlocks
It's like
Isn't the rich the American shit with it you keep twitching and noise yes, and that's what he was doing
He kept touching his nose
I don't think the thing that is and Carl are like the most powerful warlocks then I'm
I'll be okay. I'll be okay. Have they ever been on the panel at the same time? No, they might be the same person
Can you tell us about your new green screen and tell us about that eye of raw place
Well, this is my love. I also have a tattooed and it's like
The Sun and the Moon in certain ways and there's a lot of Egyptian mythology behind it as well
Also, you know, I have a show and so it's like you watch shows with their eyes
It is very like it's been looking and like watching and like that's what one of our powers most powerful things that we have this vision
Why you put a white wig on now? Are you trying to be say yourself? You're a white witch with a white wig on there?
Mr. Say
I thought it looked kind of like gem
You know, um gem in the holograms
And that's my favorite show gem gem. You're true the outrageous true the true the true the outrageous
oh the music contagion i was into the misfits more oh you are yeah they were kind of bitchy i mean
it's like i like they were bitchy but they had this slutty look to them like jam was like such a
force of good i like that and the misfits were like such a force now jam was too fucking prissy now
it was the misfits they were cool they were kind of fucking edgy you could score you could score
with the misfits jam would probably cry rape or some shit the misfits were i don't believe
Well, I believe a new key wants me to see it. What?
Okay, you know, no, I think that is I'm sorry the thing is I'm just
Basically, I can't control it comes out of people's mouths. Okay, I can like just like I can report on things
I can ask a guy said I want information about
Bronzeberg once and then I think oh you want a dog brother. No, no, no, no, I want to like
Have some kind of story to tell it like you know
Riza Riza 2.0. Have you served your country?
You cannot talk to me about being a British person Riza 2.0
Is that like prison I don't understand I'm getting big trouble
I really don't because I was like I made the song about thing that is and it's obviously I I have a good
Feeling about him like in the song
Right, anyway, can we change the conversation for the moment? Go at it.
How do you feel about the white wigs, white shoes and white plimsoes?
You should never wear them after Labor Day.
Unless unless you wear white pants and you go to the bowling alley and you have a big accent and you shit yourself
And you shit yourself all over
90 weighties the earth's tiny weighties a bit fucking words not even good as wife runs
Just another platform. It's a portal hear the announcement mystics flash with chaos live
Major change coming discover who's live right now, and who's rising step on stage
Be seen be backed by a community that gives a damn
Psycheverse.org your warp gate to the panel verse and beyond
promote your channel grow fast connect deeper
stream smarter
Ready to enter? Tap follow, go live, and ride the cosmic wave.
Join the Psycheverse, where creators become constellations.
Don't take shit from me
I got a stomach full of fingernails, another steamer on my head.
He's a thinker from the frost and pine
Head shines bright, got a reasoned mind
He'll test your words, he'll twist your view
But he'll smile when he knows he's got truth
From Canada's hush to the world's loud room
He stands his ground, clears the gloom
He'll question your gods, defend your rights
And still wish you peace at the end of the fight
Never cruel
Stands for the fair, stands for the truth
That wasn't like inside jokes or anything.
I wrote that before any of this happened.
So it's like, I was kind of watching back where it's like,
probably about his like mindset, electricity and stuff.
I mean, it's kind of like weird.
That's why kind of like fun to do these things
because it's like, I feel like it's some form of divination
with like stuff that I even,
like even if it's like there's stuff misspelled,
I think there's something to that.
I think always look for like things.
especially things that are like not normal, it seems to stand out because there's messages being
delivered to us. Some from like good sources, some from not so good. Also, that's worth the
discernment to like what messages you listen to because they're gonna have a lot of like,
oh, thank you for like, uh, you know, Jamie, thanks for renewing your membership. Awesome,
you're so sweet. Like, or yeah, there you go, remember for two months. Jamie's, yeah, I think,
AI is cyberspellcasting, yeah, it's very magical.
I mean, but it's like computers are magical
through the internet is too,
because that was like having the ability
to duplicate a message and then duplicate an image,
duplicate a media file.
Like that's also like just the record industry too.
TV, right?
Think about how magical these things are, right?
Incredibly magical because.
They can have an influence also you take it as entertainment, right?
But it's like actually there's messages being delivered
You have to be on guard of your subconscious mind as to what is the not only the person trying to say
But it's like what is like, you know your brain taking it as and the subconscious which you're feeling about some things
It's like that's why it's like, you know, I shows about examining a lot of just the consciousness and not being like
I mean, so mystified in a way, but I will say like, you know, if you do have like, you know triggers like MK ultra programming
You might want to like, you know, maybe see professional to help you deal with some of the trigger triggers
I was cooking talking about Scientology was I don't know. He probably they probably try to recruit him
Like they try to recruit all celebrities, right and they do like a big like, you know
They make it like not even about Scientology. They just like invite like have a big party for them like sit on there
Like they're cherry workers or something like that like the celebrities
They just flatter them until the celebrity like basically joins because they like the way they're treated and like no butler
I mean, that's how it works and then it's like and then all the regular
Pleads or like the normal people that are like outside for the church sign like a billion year your contract to be a slave on a boat
Probably see or or and then it's like you ever leave they'll pick at your house that I was her Cobain. Oh my gosh
I'm not even wearing the wig
I mean now I can look like it
Well, this is more like you know
What are you guys saying?
Vegan Patriot?
I'll do another poll.
I did this poll yesterday.
I was like, who's cuter?
Vegan Patriot or me?
And I lost the poll.
And it's my own, guys, it's really embarrassing.
It goes on like, you know, anybody else's channel,
like if it was on Be This Challenge,
you said who's cuter, Vegan Patriot or Psyche.
And like, I got 0%, I'd be like, oh yeah.
Like, of course, you know, that's gonna happen.
But if it's on my show,
I expect like at least like,
I don't know.
My audience hate I don't like the idea that my audience doesn't like I just don't like that
I mean it's because that my thing was like I wanted to have an audience that liked me and
Then like instead of one that hated me because it's like not only there's a lot of bad things that people hate
Oh, it's good for the algorithm. It's good. No, it's not good for like
Especially if they like, you know, I don't know. There's just things that you that are in there so like, you know
real thing. I keep taking chances on playing songs, copyrighted songs,
if there's anything. So Jake Paul is pretty good at YouTube.
I'm going to have to delete this video after the show and playing some copper and stuff.
Let's see.
Kind of interesting. I don't know.
Look at the chosen.
It wasn't an algorithm. You need to understand that first.
The images and sounds you were shown, the cryptic numbers that appeared in your recommendations,
that was a signal, a tuning fork resonating with something already inside of you.
You were chosen because you are one of the few who senses that the reality we see is just a fraction of the whole story.
A beautiful, hypnotic, but fragmented echo.
For months, you've been collecting those echoes, feeling their power without understanding the source.
Consider this video the first translation of that source.
This is not another theory or a guess.
This is the blueprint,
the very architecture of the philosophy you've been subconsciously drawn to.
What you're about to see is the key that elevates you from a mere spectator of the mystery
to an active participant in its unfolding.
The puzzle pieces are in your hands.
Now, let's begin to assemble them.
Let's talk about order, not the obvious kind you see in spiral galaxies or in the golden
ratio that so easily enchant minds enamored with superficial beauty.
I'm talking about the true order, the kind that vanishes the second you try to pin it
down, the order that nestles in the folds of apparent randomness, in the fractures of
reality, there among the prime numbers.
Ah, the primes. They're scattered across the number line with the same apparent anarchy
as stars in the sky too vast for our myopic gaze. We call them numbers, but honestly fractures
feels more accurate. Breaches in the quiet arithmetic progression, fissures in the fabric
of the cosmos, singularities that resist, that evade, that refuse to obey the banality
Why? Maybe because deep down we sense they're hiding something important, some hidden pattern,
a secret rhythm to the universe that we can't quite hear. So we count them, we map them,
we desperately search for a pattern in the chaos.
But chaos, dear listener, is Order's favorite disguise. Observe their distribution, scattered
like grains of sand swept by a whimsical wind, and yet something restrains us from
There are places where they clumped together and vast deserts where they're nowhere to be found.
It's as if they're following invisible pathways, guided by an architecture that no one ever designed.
The ancients might have chalked it up to the will of the gods, a divine plan we are not meant to understand,
or maybe they were smarter than us and just accepted the mystery for what it was.
We, on the other hand, we keep digging.
We hunt for formulas, build algorithms, and stare at graphs, hoping to find the key that
will grant us mastery over the secret.
But this secret, like those notorious grains of sand carried away by the wind, remains
elusive.
And now, let us recall singularities, those points where order folds in on itself, where
meaning crumbles, where equations cease to respond with the respect they usually grant
In the black holes of space-time, the infinite wedges itself into the finite,
and geometry ceases to be comprehensible.
And in prime numbers, the analogy is too evident not to arouse suspicion.
They do not mix with other numbers, do not allow themselves to be broken down into simpler factors.
They resist, like points where arithmetic's linearity fractures, like nodes in an invisible web
holding together the foundations of a reality we stubbornly call solid.
Because, let's be honest, we don't invent math, we discover it.
And the things we discover always seem to be echoes of something that was already there, long before we were.
So what is this bizarre, unpredictable dance of the primes trying to tell us?
If math is the language the universe speaks, what's the message?
And more importantly, why are we so determined not to listen?
Perhaps, deep down, the answer is too unsettling.
Because if prime numbers truly are fractures in order,
if they truly mark the points where reality breaks and reveals its deeper substratum,
then everything we think we know about the world is an unstable construct,
an illusion resting on a perforated grid.
Our logic, our science, our certainty that the world is a neat, solvable puzzle,
all of it shatters when you realize there are breakpoints,
glitches where the incomprehensible peeks through.
And maybe that's the real reason we're so obsessed with them.
Not so much out of a desire to know, but out of the terror of accepting that there is nothing to know.
Or, worse still, that knowledge exists, but we are not its intended recipients.
That the cosmos has left clues we are incapable of deciphering.
Or that, perhaps, with a sly grin, it has scattered a trail whose only purpose is to lead us astray.
But don't let that get you down.
The fact that you're here, watching this, means a part of you has already sensed that reality is a little fragmented.
You've already noticed the cracks.
You've already heard the faint echo of the void that hums just beneath the surface of everything.
And maybe, if you're brave enough, you'll stop searching for a pattern, and just listen.
Because sometimes, the greatest secret isn't what's hidden.
It's the mystery itself.
See you in the next episode.
And so now we're gonna deal with the anima and the anima again this refers more to the male psyche right the male psyche in
relationship to the feminine and so we've got a
Projection here of Audrey Hepburn who I can honestly say is a bit of an anima for me. She's she's a lovely lovely actress, so
So this is a clip from a film called The Secret Life of Walter Mitty and in this film it's
describing his experience of seeing the anima. So he sees the anima and then he goes into this
total fantasy of himself as the ideal ego. He's this heroic figure and he rescues her and it's
quite drawn out. So this is an example of the kind of relationship that the male ego can have
Yeah, so this is this is a great clip right because it shows us the experience of a male especially a young male
You know and these fantasies that he has about this ideal feminine, right?
So the anima is the personification of all feminine psychological tendencies in a man's psyche,
such as vague feelings and move, prophetic hunches, receptiveness to the irrational,
capacity for personal love, feeling for nature, and last but not least, his own relationship
toward the unconscious collectively.
In its individual manifestation, the character of a man's anima is as a rule shaped by his
mother.
So that's to say that the first experience of a young male is of mother.
Mother is the world, and this is the image of the sacred goddess, you know, this idea of the, you know, the sacred world goddess, Mother Earth, you know, this kind of mythic form.
Where the mother cares for the child in every way and for the for the young infantile boy
his entire libido is directed towards the mother and this really will have a huge impact on
Basing and building the foundation for the young boy's relationship towards women and even his relationship with himself
Later on in life. So if he has a bad experience of the mother, you know, this is a mother that didn't really want the child
Maybe you know that you can find this in men later on as irritable depressed moods uncertain
insecurity and touchiness. The anima repeats I am nothing. Nothing makes any
sense. With others it's different, but for me I enjoy nothing. This negative
anima appears in dreams.
As a death demon the French for my feet how right so this is this is the man
This is the man who had a negative experience of his mother and you see a lot of men like this. They have no
Feeling relationships. They have no feeling
Experiences with with life life is a very cold
Cold and factual experience for them. And so there's no projection. There's no intimacy very little life in the psyche
If instead a young boy has a good experience of his mother, perhaps even too good, he can
become effeminate or perhaps preyed upon by women, and thus is unable to cope with the
hardships of life.
This sort of an anima experience can turn men into sentimentalists, or they may become as touchy as old maids.
The effect of this anima is shown in all those neurotic, sueto-intellectual dialogues
that inhibit a man from getting into direct touch with life and its real decisions.
He reflects or thinks about life so much that he simply
doesn't live it. And I can honestly say that when I was younger, this was definitely me.
I had a really caring mother, a really caring grandmother, and I struggled as a young man to
overcome these effeminate qualities. And in fact, in my testimonial video, the one
that I did just most recently here,
talking about when I broke up with Sarah,
this negativity that came out of me
was so profoundly powerful,
because I had such a slant in my psyche
towards being incapable of dealing
with the hardships of life.
You know, as a young boy,
if you're coddled by your mother too much,
then you become, you know, very, very resentful to life
because life doesn't appease you,
it doesn't take care of you like mom did, right?
And this can create a lot of toxicity in the psyche.
balance between these two opposite extremes. And you can see this in men, in the different
relationships that men will have. So the anima is responsible
For the fact that a man is able to find the right marriage partner, the anima will function
in helping a man pull up or dig up hidden facts about his psyche. She enriches the man's life
with beauty and vitality, feeling for nature, sensitivity, compassion and spontaneity.
The most vital role played by the anima is her ability to put a man's mind in tune with the
right inner values. This functions to open the male ego up to the call of the self. She functions as
into the psyche, calling him to personal fulfillment.
We see this played out in the role of Beatrice in Dante's Paradiso.
The role of the anima is to function as mediator between the ego and the self.
So really what's being described here is that it's essential to understand that the male's
relationship with the sacred feminine, the male's relationship with this feminine image
within his mind has a direct impact on his relationship towards his spirituality, his
relationships, every aspect of his intuitive life is really built on this relationship
with this feminine aspect of himself. This is so key to understanding male psychology.
The anima likewise will follow four stages in her development.
The initial phase is the erotic phase, and this is of course started in adolescence when a young boy is first experiencing this projection.
I mean, at the beginning the anima is formed by his experience of his mother,
but then around the ages of 13, 14, 15, suddenly his libido will turn away from mother, sometimes in a very aggressive way,
young girls around his age and this is the experience of the awakening
of sexuality. And as the young boy grows up, you know, and he gets a little older,
his romantic feelings will begin to develop. Now again, this is directly proportional to his
experience of his mother. Many men never reach this phase. They will never reach the romantic
phase. You know, the idea of romance never impacts them at any time. And so this is represented
Finally, this is when we enter the third stage, and this is love,
libido, eros, and this is really the male who has matured, and so he is raised up out of the erotic and
becomes orientated towards spiritual devotion, so the Virgin Mary or Kwan Yin, the Buddhist.
So this is a phase in which the male recognizes the anima, this ideal feminine form that he's been pursuing since his youth,
to be a spiritual truth, rather so much a
a major development, a very hard stage to overcome. And finally, if he can go even further,
he will arrive at the final stage, which is to recognize the anima as wisdom incarnate.
Open. Out in the open, wisdom calls aloud. She raises her voice in the public square.
The Christian tradition Christ was referred to as wisdom while in the Old Testament wisdom is a feminine figure
So you could talk about Christ as much as as a woman as you can a male
Which I think may come as a shock to a lot of people the the in the East in the Orient
They have Prajnaparamita, which is a female kind of goddess figure who is responsible for containing and maintaining
The the mythology of wisdom. She is she is the book. She is the wisdom teachings of the
Buddha, the incarnation of his insight.
And so the male has to recognize the spiritual forms of wisdom to be the ultimate holy expression.
of the sacred feminine within himself. Here we have Hagia Sophia. This was at one time the
largest church in the world. It's built in Constantinople, which unfortunately was conquered
by the Muslims, and it's been since turned into a mosque. But this idea of God as sacred feminine
here, as Mary, you know, and the Christ child himself, as the feminine wisdom incarnate,
represents that this is a deeply symbolic notion that we find great expression of in Christianity.
perfection. She holds the books of the wisdom of enlightenment. In the Catholic
tradition, Nuestra Maude, our holy mother, you know, I actually had the
pleasure of going down and seeing Arley Guadalupe on her feast day, and to see
the crowds of people to come out and pay homage to this image, you know, to this
to this.
representation of the sacred feminine. It's really beautiful. These were some
photographs that I actually took myself when I was there and you can see the
outpouring of religious feeling towards this, you know, which is rather
it's rather controversial because you have to consider that these are
Catholics and ultimately their commitment is to Christ, but you can
definitely see that the sacred feminine in the form of the Virgin Mary has found
great and beautiful expression within the Catholic faith.
And then we have Kuan Yin, and this is the incarnation of Avalokiteshvara, the Buddha of Compassion,
a symbol of the sacred feminine within the Orient, within the East.
Here you have some more images of Quan Yin, beautiful iconography.
Now this is a short piece out of the movie, The Lord of the Rings, the Fellowship of the Ring.
It's the scene when Arwen comes in and sees Frodo.
And I can honestly say when I was a teenager this movie came out.
And I think this was the first moment that I had, you know, watching this film.
It was a kind of rapture that came over me.
And it was the idea of this sacred...
Kind of pure female energy that was just so compelling. I remember you know watching the scene and being really moved by it
So we'll give it a watch here
And I want you to try and pull out the the sacred feminine the the goddess-like imagery that comes through here
Beautiful scene, you know, and it captures this this idea of the sacred feminine quite nicely
So here we have the sacred feminine as mother nature, you know
So I'm going to read for you guys here
This is a letter that was sent by chief Seattle to the president of the United States and
this was at a time when the Americans were coming out into the into the native's country and
He writes this letter to the president and it says
The president in Washington sends word that he wishes to buy our land
But how can you buy or sell the sky the land?
The idea is strange to us.
If we do not own the freshness of the air and the sparkle of the water, how can you buy them?
Every part of the earth is sacred to my people.
Every shining pine needle, every sandy shore, every mist in the dark woods,
every meadow, every humming insect, all are holy in the memory and the experience of my people.
We know the sap which courses through the trees as we know the blood that courses through our veins
We are part of the earth and is part of us
The perfume flowers are our sisters the bear the deer the great eagle
These are our brothers the rocky crests the dew in the meadow
The body heat of the pony and man all belong to the same family
The shining water that moves in the streams and rivers is not just water, but it is the blood of our ancestors.
If we sell you our land, you must remember that it is sacred.
Each glossy reflection in the clear waters of the lakes tells of events and memories in the life of my people.
The water's murmur is the voice of my father's father.
The rivers are our brothers. They quench our thirst. They carry our canoes and feed our children.
So you must give the rivers the kindness that you would give any brother.
If we sell you our land, remember that the air is precious to us, that the air shares its spirit with all the life that it supports.
The wind that gave our grandfather...
Psych yeah, I'm here. Oh, hey, sorry. My computer just froze for a second. Hang on
Well, yeah, that's not a bit Sharon we might have like over life lifetimes
Are we good, okay, I'm back to live are we good can you hear me? Okay?
Sorry about that and wisdom also is it wisdom is something that you learn through like experience
You know, it's like not if you can't it's not just taught
You know knowledge is taught wisdom is that you have to kind of like learn yourself
And so that's why it's like harder one, but it's like more valuable. It's just pure knowledge
my
Yeah, so let's address the elephant in the room like I played up a bit what happened earlier for you for a little drama
It was a little shocking like that. You know that you seem to be okay with it
Not like that freaked out about it either. I wouldn't say I didn't when I hear someone say I would like that person's name
I would like a more think about
they wanted not to dox them, like officially, I mean, I don't think, well, I hope she would.
But why does she need to know my real name? I don't need to know hers. I mean, I assume
she's going by her real name, but I don't really care if she were going by a different name.
This dox by a Canadian man, I know, I think, and then it's like, you know, so she was basically maybe...
Little traumatized by that and maybe like it's prejudiced. I'm not sure for 100%
I don't want to like put words in her mouth or her thoughts or whatever
I'm just for just one more I see I think that it's like she might have a problem with you
Just because she doesn't know you and it's like there's something else like
You know if notion or something about people from Canada, I'm not 100% sure I think
That you should maybe try to like address like a talk talk to her in her chat or something like that
And like because I think we should all meet people should meet each other and like then make the judgment rather than
Just I haven't been mean to her in chat like as far as addressing her directly. I haven't been mean or
Anything I don't even recall addressing her directly in chat. I've addressed her
When she was on panel with you
And I've addressed you when she's been in chat before,
but I don't think I've ever actually addressed her directly.
Well, I mean, it's like on panel, we were once at the very, very beginning of all of this.
We were on panel at briefly.
Right.
And I think Bita asked me my opinion.
I said, I don't really know her.
I don't know.
But since then, plenty of stuff has happened.
you know from what I see it's
Good, so I'm just I
I'm giving my opinion on it. The star is definitely rising because first you were clipped on that
You know on the other show and stuff and it's like so people are just taking notice of you just like
You know, I think like some people's kind of like, you know, didn't go through this like portal or something where it's like
They're just like furthers. There's a lot like karmic stuff happening and like a lot of but I think I do feel like it rides for me
Like a more like a recognize ability and so maybe that's like the vibe
I do think you're a powerful person, right?
I
Realize that my communication ability is is fairly decent so
maybe
because I can use different words, you know, at different times.
I can express myself more specifically.
You look like kind of smart, like really smart.
And I think while you might have been just like, you know, like smiling at the chat
or smiling at the chat or something like that,
it might seem like, you know, you're like,
I have like a little bit of mastermind or something energy
that kind of will make some people uncomfortable because they'll think it's like, you know.
Any influence I have.
Use for good.
It has come from whatever those people give me. I haven't gone looking for influence. I'm just being myself
People and if people think that whatever I say means something well, you're magnetic. That's that's pretty cool
Well spoken. I mean it's again also like, you know, and it's especially this university intelligent people like or people that speak very well
And like, you know, I do believe like a lot of people are intelligent, but sometimes they don't speak that
I mean, I admit, I haven't been, you know, whatever I have said about Alexander that I've said in other chats or in your chat hasn't been flattering, I, but I've only talked about her position on the, on the, what's it called on the scale.
Yeah.
And so hopefully you can work that out.
I don't know man, she just threatened to go private,
so I don't know, why should I?
And all the shit she's doing to beat,
I mean, she's freaking out of her mind.
Like I don't see why I would ever have
a decent relationship with her.
I think it's time to like have a talk,
like to like get things on the table.
I don't believe in like cutting all of a sudden
cutting people off and then just having all the...
I'm not saying who's doing that, but it's them who's saying like it looks like how like a talk and like cash it out
And don't be afraid to talk to your adversary because maybe you can actually I
Don't consider her an adversary. I don't consider her at all
Like except for when when I see things like this when someone tells me something about her
Or when something happens, it's the only time and that's the only reason she's doing it. She wants my attention
I mean, it's very clear
So
Yeah, I think you're a good for me. I just felt I don't feel like you're you're doing bad things
But it's like when Joe said that and say if you don't and she knows but the thing is she knows Joe
So she kind of doesn't know that Joe's cable say that stuff
But we also see that Joe is kind of like a blank slate like you tell me isn't that drunk say how easy to manipulate or how much she's
Like trying to find yeah acceptance by being outrageous and like you know
Let's say I was all the most outrageous thing you can say that I'm gonna like what he said to me, too
He's like all SLIT my throat, and I'll I'm gonna break your NACK. I'm gonna run your award
Yeah, he's nuts and even when Alex says this shit man, like when I'm just in chat
Oh, you usually be like oh man frown or say like chill Alex or Joe chill, whatever, you know when this shit happens
But like I've told you at the beginning
Uh, I honestly don't remember that him saying that
Well, I don't because it's kind of like a thing that would unless you're just like so used to him saying stuff like that
But it's like that you would just not notice. Well, that's the thing. He was pretty much blocked out at that point
Like I could I obviously could tell that he was saying something. I just wasn't absorbing the words
It seems well, I just wanted to get your side your your opinion on it
I don't do more of the clips and stuff
I mean, I don't, I'm not a violent person.
I don't like violence.
I wanna see what's being said,
so you can address it, like, basically, and so.
Yeah, okay, well, I saw it, and.
Well, there's more to it, like,
because I wanna see, like, your body language a little bit.
Like, if you got an oratory to track a little bit.
Cause it's like, I wanna see how it's gonna interpret it,
and like, you know, it's just, and like, why?
Let me see, so it's a little bit.
Um, okay, so it's on this
And I hope
I mean
What were we doing that night? It looks like we were playing trivia, right?
But you see this, okay
And she by the way does have a show going right now, and I hope she's not mad at me or something
She's a couple of times Alexander Alexander talks to you. Well, yeah, and please I want her to
But anyway, so here's the rest of this clip.
So what's happening? Are you going to play something?
Really as you want she cannot touch you legally due to this
And it's not a thing that is who said it.
It was an American and we know exactly where the American lives.
We know everything about him.
We don't hate him though.
His mind is weak.
It's this one right here.
Right here.
Watch his face.
Just watch.
Trivia Alex out there you you bitch
He's not flinching nothing
It sounded like I was answering chat so I obviously read something in his mouth isn't that's what I was doing there
Because I said trivia Alex or whoever whatever name is on what you believe in in this world
again compulsion
complaining
No
He does interact a little bit, but it's like he's the one saying it instead of Joe
Joe is very easy to manipulate. Listen to what she's saying. She's saying that
My words are being spoken by Joe as if I put them in his mouth
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Shut up, Joe. Can you shut the fuck up? I can't leave her. I'm gonna have to go like brush my teeth.
Are you trying to make that yasho?
No, it's not.
I'm actually like my own like my issue and it's like this is that really stupid and I gotta get it out of my head is like
I trust it like like I try to help and trust somebody and like I think Mimi really hurt me
I think that's what it is me me me me me me me me
It's not about you most of Favi. It hasn't been but
Why do you keep using her real name? You're looking at some lawsuits. You might even be looking at prison time at this point
You're inciting violence against
I just did a live stream saying hey, I'm not gonna interfere
I didn't say was the dog I said why does she keep using her first her real last name? That was what I asked
I don't answer what I asked
I don't I don't know what the purpose of it and do you think it's it's it's okay because I've asked you this before and you
You hedged man. You went all around you danced all around
Here you go, okay, here you go again, I want your opinion your opinion
See you're evading again you will not lay any blame on Alexandria at all at all
and that's just because she is absolutely batching insane and you are fucking listening to her as if
she's some sort of goddess or whatever that uh what was that thing in Greece you know the
Oracle like as if she's some she's some kind of Oracle. She's just insane psych. That's all that's absolutely all it's that there is
Feminine intuition and she may have like see them in an intuition. Okay, fine
What if that female is insane though that intuition is gonna be so
Like hers is
Clinical assessment here, okay, I think we all understand what I'm talking about
Okay, and Sharon says, when it's Alice investor time and knowledge in a project, she fully expects AW, when her investors get sidetracked, it says struggle to see her vision to completion.
And she's not speaking for Alexandra.
Alexandra.
And no, I don't, I mean, Alexandra is very like, has a PI, like kind of like journalistic energy, where it's like that kind of stuff.
It doesn't really surprise me like, wait, it doesn't like, I think that journalists will always try to.
It doesn't matter.
I don't think that I don't think necessarily the doctor doesn't matter her her outcomes her her leaps are fucking insane
Her leaps of logic and the conclusions she comes to are just well
Spiritual people like well, you know, I believe that she's here with the same
So it's like there is a spiritual aspect to things and like that
I thought other people will see and I'm not necessarily saying that that's true in this situation
But I say like sometimes we don't be very confident in our abilities to see like kind of past the veil sometimes and can be very confident in our
Conclusions that sometimes I'm going to say I do a lot, but it's my hundred percent right now, right?
It's like so I just have to be set to be open to the possibility of like maybe we're mistaken
Maybe we're we'll come to some other understanding like if we know the person there
I don't know. I'm just like a peacemaker. I think about man
Just just fucking say that this shit that she says is pretty is pretty out there and you don't
Quest for
going after private info of individuals and using private info.
Well, that's like that's like actually like sometimes, you know
For people that are people that are doing things like why can't you thank you. You wanted me to
Joe you wanted me to take some kind of responsibility for what Joe was saying just because I was on the the screen at the same time
But that's that's exactly what it what it looks like right
that i'm responsible for what joe was saying that i
Is mine right that is what she is saying in the freaking clip. Do you agree?
We all have the right to have our own opinions and conclusions
Do you agree that she was saying in the clip that i put the words in joe's mind?
her opinion those
My opinion. No, that's why maybe one of the reasons we're in a little bit of it. I'll tell you right now because
You know, I'm I don't think there's anything wrong with that.
You want she has no responsibility at all, right?
She, you know, you you go along with everything she does, man.
That that's totally cool because she pats you on the head.
So I mean, I'm going to be pats you on the head.
This is the only fucking reason why you're following her.
Otherwise, you would be more rational and be like, Jesus, I'm not rational.
Also, you know, just like you said, just like you said, you know, beat is like, you know,
She's a good friend of yours and you're gonna be on her side no matter what basically I didn't say no matter what I don't think I ever said that
No, I would never say that no matter what that's a that's a retarded thing to say
I mean like you know, but it seems like
You're you pick you're like on side. It's when you're on a side. You're gonna be biased towards that side
So everything. Yes, that's why I said I'm on beta side because I am biased towards beta
That that kind of goes in conjunction, right?
Why would I be biased towards Alexandra and be on beta side?
Well, I mean, it's like that's not neutral though. It's like, you know, Canada's supposed to be neutral or that's what I didn't say
I was a neutral in everything. I said I was I was being neutral between beta and you
And you know what? That's what I think what really happens is like, I don't want to be responsible
I want you to I don't want you to respond to what Joe says
I don't want to be responsible for all of them. So like everybody has their own. Okay
So then you accept Alexander as a video is just nonsense, right? Well, my opinion
that um there's you admit that you admit it's just not it's just the blabberings of a of a
raven unit right yeah however she wants yeah yes she could state it however she wants
it's what can get smeared on a wall but whatever my opinion on this one uh with judging you about it
She might
If it's my intelligence or something that's threatening her then
If it's my my appearance that's threatening her tough shit, it's not my fault
If my words are fending her well then let me know what my words are and then maybe I can work on that but
On shit that I can't do anything about. Just shut the fuck up
I'm not even a streamer Sharon like I don't know why she's focusing on me man
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I've been going on panels really just you in betas, but I've been on a couple of others
Panels are like
Some of the crazier panel right or can't yeah, mine's yeah, and when it gets nuts, I usually try and stay out of it
I usually
Kind of goes crazy, but um, no, I laugh I still laugh I just don't take it off
I think it's like
Like we expect they especially like you know some women would like they're they're threatening stuff. They'd like to see
man just not like sit there and like you know be distracted by the chat they
want to see like of the man that kind of like
Coming to the I don't care. I'm not interested in Alexander's. So I don't care what she wants
Oh, no, no, that sounded like a genuine threat if my information does all of a sudden pop up
I'll know exactly why and I will feed that video to the police up here. I mean, that's that's guaranteed. I promise you that
No, no
It was real. It was real. Okay. Those things have repercussions. That was real. Don't give me this this shit
When she says this ludicrous shit that I'm controlling people and I'm responsible for other people's words
That stuff is nonsense
But saying I will give anything to have his real name
That is
Um, she was just like, you know, and this, I mean, I, I mean, but I
Stop them and hawing and fucking stand up for something.
That's amazing.
Is it okay what she's doing, or it's not good what she's doing?
Say something.
I'm not responsible for what other people say, you know, and say, I'm, but I'm seeking
up for you.
I'm not asking you to take responsibility.
I'm asking for your opinion.
My opinion.
Do you disagree with what she's doing, or do you disagree with what she's doing?
I'm not telling you what can take responsibility for it.
I'm against doxing, but I'm not going to say anything beyond I'm against doxing.
And so it's like, you know, that sort of thing is covered in there.
I don't need to give personal opinions about, oh, this person is right or wrong.
OK. OK. Listen, so you would be OK if I took away from this conversation
that you are OK with doxing because you won't.
I just said I'm not OK.
I just said I'm doing what I should say.
I'm not OK with doxing.
Okay, so you can pick anything else you want from there.
So, you know, I don't have to say anything about anybody.
Whoever's Docs is not good to Docs.
But is the last name a Docs?
No.
Is an address a Docs?
Yes.
Is the phone number a Docs?
But I don't think necessarily names are,
especially when the name has been out there publicly
for a long time, like maybe over eight years, you know?
It's like, which is like how long Vita's been on.
So, I mean, it's like, her name's been out there.
She even said her own last name on her show.
when I was on, when she was interviewing me.
She even says it, so her name's already out there,
and I mean, it is like a rare name, you know, officially.
We've had this conversation already.
I think last time I was up here talking to you about this,
that, yes, I realize Bita's name,
it has been out there for a while.
It's not technically Doxing,
but Bita doesn't go by her last name, does she?
Like she had nowhere online does she actually go by her last name like her channels don't use her last name at all that kind of shit right so for someone to constantly be using it in a known feud with that person is such as fuck you don't think.
Um, I mean it's like during the conflicts conflicts can get messy, right?
And so it's like uh, and then except for me done and said like that
Maybe it's like outside of the realm of like, you know acceptable warfare, but you know to be all all the rules of warfare like more
You know
There you go, uh, just fucking evading again
What I asked those are messy broken. That's the person who I think that okay, so you're okay with that then
Well, you know as they know not with you. I mean it's a these are the case-by-case basis
So you don't draw the line at private stuff even though you yourself are going through stuff
in your private life.
Perhaps me and a young person.
A young person. I don't care what Doc's saying.
He's the person that's doing this to me.
So that's why I put his name in a song, I mean.
But I realized his last name.
Because he's like sending people like scrap metal workers
and people looking for lawn mowers
and pizza and a fertilizer to my house
all the time. Like every day I'm getting people to my house.
And so I don't care saying his last name.
Even though it may piss him off and stuff like that.
He also has a whole
whole YouTube channel with my front door on it, with him ordering pizzas like on
tape or like you know he's like just the taping when they come to my house and stuff like that
they say oh he's another delivery he's on case admitting that he's sending the scram
middle people over there I mean it's like so he's right so why would you want to start that cycle
for somebody else or potentially start with potentially start jumping in the middle of
their of their conflicts because it's their conflict I don't I'm not part of the conflict
that's the whole thing is like I just wanted to stay out of that and have been in relationships.
Like I don't like, I don't like how Bea's treated me the whole time, like all the time,
or even how she's treating me now, which I think is pretty bad. Like you know she's got Bronsburg,
Katie and like all these things, all these like little people in the chat like she wants around
her and then it's like I was actually her friend and it's like you know she's just like treats me
I mean that's been for a while and so there's more stuff to like and so that I was trying to like basically like not leave it
At that I didn't want to leave it a horrible state
I needed to talk to her a few times and now I now I know it's like okay
Well, you know, I tried but give it a gallon effort to at least be in a friendship. I'm not in love with her
You know, I'm not in love with any woman or I guess that's Alexander
I'm not in love with any woman or man or you know anybody I'm a
It's like self-partner and so I'm not really like
looking for like
You know anyone to date or falling in love, but I do romanticize sometimes especially but it's more like a goddess worship kind of I
Think you do have infatuations on them
I don't think it's love love like romantic love, but I think you're infatuated with them, right?
It's not a sexual thing. It's like, you know, I just like really respect like, you know, like strong women and things like that
and
You know, I think women are like, I respect women for bringing
you know, children to the world too, or like, you know,
and making the women that get pregnant,
making that sacrifice, because I think it's a big sacrifice,
you know, the time and like, of their body and stuff like that
to bring a baby to the world.
And so even if people don't like their mother,
it's like, I think the mother at one point, like, you know,
and it's also the mother's love, right?
Which is like, even like, you know, the child could be a monster
and they shall still like, you know, remember like him.
Or you don't have to...
like preach to me about this stuff. I'm perfect. I respect women. I learned that well when I was young.
I'm saying that wasn't like, you know, you didn't come to Alexandra's defense as a woman for saying,
I mean, someone's like saying that they're gonna unalive them. And that's what I'm saying. It's like, you know,
that would be like something that would like maybe like...
Have been nice instead of like just sitting there or you know, but maybe you weren't sure I
Don't owe her that and like I said, I don't remember Joe saying that I accept him saying it
But I don't remember it happening happening
And I don't owe her anything to defend her. Okay
Well, yeah, and that's why just like people don't mean anything. They don't have people that don't defend me
But like in the summers like for example summer would be like, you know, oh, well, I'd be a beat his name
I'm not talking about and I'm talking to be a and then um, so then
I'd bring then but then
Todd they're talking about me. She's fine to be on the panel talking about me and stuff
Oh, I'm not hired to talk about people seem afraid of me or at least one summer man. None of this has anything to do with me
Okay, so that's what you want in this in whatever's going on between
I want to know I want trying to get your position so you're gonna be like
Like me for example between beta and you just neutral. You're not gonna really go after either side
Okay, so you're gonna be
that everything else right how many times do I have to say I get it yeah I get it okay so now
we know where you stand so in the future if something were to happen and you were to lean on
either side we could say hey psych what happened to be neutral are you now taking sides that's what
every time I said anyway no one ever defends me um so but if that were to happen you you'd be okay
Because that goes with the territory of being neutral, is that if you do change your career
and you're sitting on panels when you're face out on shows, even if you don't give your name
and stuff, you're going to get the, especially if you're on a, this is like Dawson community,
which is like this, just a panel versus a very well known.
Little bit, but it's okay. No, no, no
What what I've said is that her seeking my private info is outrageous, right?
Her just talking about me and thinking I'm whatever and all that shit is just batching insane to me
I don't care like I told beta just ignore her
Her flicking insane like her insanity will be her own downfall and it's proving true. So why the hell why would I be mad at her?
I don't care
Maybe we'll all just agree, disagree, and...
You know, it's like, I mean, I just like, I love all you guys, you know, it's like, so, well, that's fine
I don't want to be in the middle of I like most people too. Yeah, I'm in the middle of most people
I'm not gonna like everybody. You're not gonna like everybody. So
We've come across somebody that I'm not that fond of at the moment. So there we go
Well, hopefully maybe you can have this conversation and maybe we'll
I want to end I'm gonna stop talking about it. I'm gonna soon end the stream because you know, I don't feel like
I feel like bad talking about her and it's like she's not here to defend herself.
Okay.
I'll let you up for 30 days.
But I want to say, you know, but she, I think she is live if anyone wants to talk.
No kicking out trolls. Listen, it's like before you go just acknowledge a little bit. I didn't bring her up in all this
Right, you started playing that video and kind of wanted mine. I'll take all the heat for everything
Okay, so like I wasn't bringing her up. I wasn't gonna talk about her at all
Okay, your response so we can have that and it's like and then you know
That's why I want to be kind of like like the news kind of like impartial a little bit, but but thank you for being on
I love you. Okay
Alright man, I'll talk to you later, go on to drop down, okay?
Okay.
Alright, have a good night.
Um, yeah, I'm just gonna, well, time to take off the wig, it's gonna be a little bit itchy,
and uh, um, I'll be back later, I'm just like, oh, do I have a coffee left, yeah, I don't
want a coffee left, maybe, I don't know, I'll be back later, um, just, uh, I have to make
a phone, pre-phone call and do some stuff, so, oh, thank you guys, I love you, um, and
Okay, yeah
of night golden wings glowed in the candle light crowds came running just to see the
flame but envy was the price of fame and now he stands where the echoes fall with tarot
in hand hearing every call from praise to venom in the same